My god!
Oh, yeah.
And that was my sound, by the way.
The Windows sound.
I connected my body to the computer, so I can completely immerse myself in whatever I'm about to experience.
I'm ready.
Are you ready?
Where have I heard that?
That's been on my mind lately.
Um, hold on a minute.
Holy bejesus.
BQ.
An evil... Jesus.
They both gave out 20 community subs.
Holy shit.
And a bunch of other people subscribed as well.
You guys are excited for Animal Well, huh?
Damn!
Thank you.
And congrats to all the people who got it.
Oh my god.
And now Sparv as well.
Guys.
The longer you sub for, the less time there is to game.
You know?
Just telling you that.
But I'm so excited about it.
I appreciate it, guys.
Thank you.
I'm so glad Animal Well won the vote.
That's good.
I mean, we're playing it now.
It was very close, though.
Closely followed by... I was about to say Slay the Spire.
Slay the Princess.
And...
The Binding of Isaac.
Yeah.
It was super close.
I cannot believe people just gifted 20 gift subs.
Two of them.
And then Sparv as well at the end there.
And a bunch of other people.
Jared Todd.
Just Bryson.
Gave out two community subs as well.
I can't even keep up here.
And Tambor Lane comic as well.
I actually can't keep up with it.
It's... I feel bad about that.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to keep up with it.
Where these votes happen?
Um...
On StrawPoll.
But I link it on my YouTube and also in my Discord.
When it's time to vote.
And sometimes I'll mention it on stream as well.
And give a link there.
Yeah.
Got no idea what this game is at all.
I'm excited.
It could be anything.
Yeah, me too!
I mean, obviously I logged into the menu yesterday.
Just to, you know, make sure everything was working.
And immediately I was like, I gotta make a waiting screen with like a CRT effect.
I love that art style.
Or not the art style.
That retro effect.
Very fancy.
I love it.
So obviously I had to do that.
It's about animals and wells.
I have a feeling you're lying.
I feel like there's probably not gonna be...
any wells in this game.
You could turn the CRT effect off under options.
Yeah, I saw that.
I saw there was an option for scan lines.
But I prefer it on.
Looked way better with it on.
At least the menu.
The colors are great.
It's inspired by some artwork I found on Google Images of Animal Well.
I'm assuming there's gonna be a cat in the game?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Apparently it was a bit unofficial.
I remixed it a little bit to my own liking.
Changed it up in Photoshop and stuff.
Playing without a guide is a must for this one.
8x to go for me.
I don't know what that means.
But I'm not intending to use a guide.
I'm just gonna play the game.
As it was presented to me.
You know?
I bought the game on Steam.
I'm gonna play the game.
See what happens.
Did you need to uninstall BF6 to install Animal Well?
You know what's funny?
No.
I didn't.
Because this game is only 30 megabytes.
What the fuck?
How is that even possible?
In this day and age.
Of unoptimized graphics and compression.
That's almost unheard of.
Yeah.
It's insane.
In this economy?
Exactly.
I heard that Call of Duty, whatever it's called, Black Ops, you know, the Battle Royale?
It was like over 100 gigabytes.
And that was five years ago or something?
It's insanity.
And again, of course, these are different games in different scope, but still.
I still can't believe that they made Mario 64 on the Nintendo fit in a couple megabytes, I think?
I don't actually remember the exact number, but it's insanely small.
And that game is actually kind of huge.
Flobby disc game, yeah.
Would be so cool if you actually sold flopby discs with the game on it.
Wouldn't it?
That would be so fitting.
Billy Basso?
Oh, is that the developer?
Solo developer, right?
Yeah, indie games are great.
I'm loving them, too.
I've been playing more of them lately.
Meaning, in the last couple years.
But most of my life, I was a competitive gamer, mostly.
Playing games like Counter-Strike, Battlefield, StarCraft.
Stuff like that.
Also, not Overwatch, but what is the other one called?
Valorant.
That one, too.
PvP in WoW, yeah.
You can actually find my PvP videos on my YouTube channel, as well.
They're unlisted, but they're in a playlist somewhere.
And I was quite high-ranked, as well, I might add.
Alright?
I was doing well for myself.
You know, the old-school PvP videos?
With the cringe rock music and all that?
That's not very cringe, but it's just, you know...
What you did at the time.
Ha ha ha ha.
I've not played Team Fortress 2, actually.
Mario 64 was 8 megabytes?
That's crazy.
Yeah, I...
It was definitely the megabyte range.
Sub 10.
Twitch tells me this stream has one viewer.
Congrats on the record, Oliver.
Thanks!
Thank you for being here, Rusted Bell.
I don't know what I would do without you.
BlindTF2?
Why would I play that blind?
There's no story or anything.
There's nothing to spoil, right?
Isn't that a multiplayer game?
It's a competitive game.
What do you think about how much game there is in Blueprints?
I love it!
I am continuously blown away by it.
I actually can't believe it.
So, what about this game, huh?
Animal Well.
I...
Let me explain what I expect here.
I know it's a puzzle game.
There's retro effects.
I'm pretty sure it's a 2D scroller.
And...
I'm not sure how long it'll be, or...
What to expect, really.
If there's any combat or what.
No idea.
I guess we'll find out.
I guess I'm expecting Hollow Knight.
But with some puzzles.
But I could be completely off here.
We'll see.
Animal Well, see.
I think I'm ready to start playing this game.
Hopefully I did this right.
Let me see.
If I can make the transition.
Oh, by the way, guys.
Before I start.
Where should the chat be?
Bottom left, top left, top right, or bottom right?
I don't know if it's gonna cover up...
Certain UI elements.
Because I didn't really check that yet.
I'm gonna fix it.
Center!
Oh, no.
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
I'm just gonna...
Someone said bottom right.
I'm gonna put it in bottom right.
And we'll see if that works.
Let's see here.
I can also...
Yeah.
Full screen the chat and then put the game in the bottom right.
That sounds horrible.
I do top right?
I can also do top right.
Yeah, we can do top right.
That's fine.
Of course, I'll check as soon as I get in.
But, yeah.
Okay.
Let's see.
Look at that menu screen.
Isn't that incredible?
Really nice atmosphere.
I'm liking that.
Okay.
Let me move this over here.
Get everything set up.
Okay.
I think we may be ready.
Controller is working.
It is not working.
What?
Why not?
Animal well.
Ah, there we go.
Okay.
Options.
Everything should be...
the way it should.
By the way, real quick.
The music right now with my voice.
Is the balance good?
I just want to get a feeling.
Because I didn't change anything with the audio yet.
It's good?
Okay.
Lovely.
I also want you guys to hear the music and stuff.
And whatever else is going to happen.
Okay.
I have no idea what's going to happen.
This is going to be great, I think.
Let's see.
Oh, hold on.
I need to savor this moment.
It's always a special moment when you start a new game, isn't it?
Okay, I'm ready.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's analyze the menu screen.
There's bunnies.
Okay.
We did it.
Go.
I don't think I will.
I'm sleeping in today.
This is so cozy.
Are those fireflies?
I'm not sure.
If they are, they're all dead.
Because they're falling down.
Oh, look at that!
You know what's funny?
This reminds me of Pac-Man.
Oh, I love the style.
Lovely little vibration in the controller when I jump.
Oh!
The bunny ran off.
Can I do things?
Oh, inventory.
I have three hearts left out of four.
That's the menu.
That's also the menu.
Okay.
Just clicking all the buttons.
Oh, look.
I can move my eyes up and down.
That's funny.
I'm playing with a PlayStation controller.
Wait a minute.
Before I move to the right.
There's got to be a secret here.
Fucking knew it.
I'm a genius.
Oh!
I thought I could climb on this.
Oh, I love this art style!
A little!
Chest.
Found clover egg.
Nice.
How do I select it?
Hmm.
Okay.
Is that a door?
Whoops.
Can I wall jump?
Nope.
Oh!
Look at the physics!
Can I jump on these pillars?
Hold on.
This can be done.
We move it.
We wait for it to swing back.
Go!
Come on.
Oh, we can't stand on it.
Oh, that would have been so good though, right?
There's something up to the left.
Wait a minute.
I think there's small versions of me on those pillars.
God, this art style is actually off the charts.
Really cool.
Oh, the reflections in the water too.
How is this game 30 megabytes?
Do I die?
I got stunned, but I didn't lose any HP, it seems.
Okay.
Nice sound effect.
Wait a sec.
Can I swim?
Like, actually?
No, I get sent up.
Okay.
Oh no, please tell me there's a map.
Otherwise, I'm gonna be so lost.
Whoops.
I keep pressing Y for some reason.
I don't know why I'm doing that.
Is that a safe?
Up.
No.
Can't make that jump.
Wait, how am I getting over there?
Okay, so I hit the ceiling when I do that.
Maybe I jump from a little further down.
I can also move quite further right here.
Like...
Nah, we can't make it.
No double jump either.
But wait a sec.
Waterfall!
Whee!
Okay.
That's funny.
I guess we go up.
Telephone?
Hello, would you like to save progress?
Over.
Save.
Speaking of floppy disks.
Um.
Man, the first thing I'm thinking of when I hear this music is Twin Peaks.
In a good way.
This is lovely.
Oh.
I didn't even see you there.
Was that a bunny?
Again?
I love this.
Little physics.
Oh.
So I can move this way.
And I...
Okay, let's not get lost.
Wait, what is this?
Can I...
Can I somehow face through the platform?
The bumpers do nothing.
Okay.
Can I...
Excuse me, I would like to save again.
Okay, there we go.
Um...
I guess I'm gonna go left.
I have a feeling that right is always the...
main path forward in video games, right?
So...
Crank.
Oh.
Doesn't that look like a face?
Someone who's crying.
That's sad.
Oh!
It's timed.
Wait, what?
Blocked.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
How do I get back?
Oh, no.
I'm in trouble here.
Okay, so I guess squares interact.
Oh!
Down...
How do I go down?
Down here, maybe?
Okay.
Yeah, I'm not...
I'm not sure what's going on here.
I'm gonna go this way.
Very pretty.
Oh.
Oh, I'm in the bottom left.
I see.
Ah, and then I'm back here.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, I clicked two buttons.
So I need to click two more buttons?
Oh, yeah.
There's a button up on the right.
I see that.
But I can't jump on these lamps, it seems.
Whoops.
So I gotta get up there somehow.
Let's try from the other side.
Whoa.
Uh-oh.
Oh!
That's bad!
Okay.
I thought it was a power-up.
Shit.
Excuse me.
Tag support.
We have an issue in the right room.
Okay, so I gotta run here.
Is it coming after me?
Doesn't seem to be the case.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, we need three.
Okay.
Cool.
Now I crank this bastard.
Nice!
Pretty good.
I love that the weight is also accelerating the downfall of it.
Pick firecracker.
Found.
Throw.
I got three out of three.
Hold on, I'm getting a message.
Oh, oh.
Is the game too low?
I can turn that up a bit.
Give me a moment.
I thought it was fine.
I asked before.
I got a Discord message.
Is it quiet?
I'll turn it up just a little bit.
Maybe you can also hear Jackie in the background.
Okay.
I can turn up the...
a little bit.
Like that.
It should be a little louder now.
I also turned it up in OBS.
Okay, so I got firecrackers.
I'm assuming I can use that to scare away animals.
Shit.
In the well.
Where is this well, anyway?
Wait a minute.
Right.
That takes it out.
Hmm.
I'm not sure what the deal is yet here.
What am I...
trying to do?
Oh, look at that.
We actually have a bunny up here on the left.
And a space invader on the right.
And there's some kind of Mayan pyramid in the center.
I'm not sure what's happening there.
Maybe animals are ruling the world.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Firecracker!
Oh, yeah.
You got st...
Stunned by that!
Nice!
Okay.
That's how you do that.
Easy peasy.
Lemon squeezy.
Man, they give me a lot of firecrackers.
Unfortunately, I can't carry anymore.
Can I walk up on this?
Oh, okay.
I thought I could walk on the purple thing up top there.
But I think that's part of the background.
Where am I?
Bottom left.
Okay.
So now we can go over here, I guess, and scare this guy off?
He's not gonna appear?
What's this?
I'm trying to decipher what's happening in the background.
Some kind of green smoke.
Oh, here we go.
No!
That's right!
Oh, I love the effects of the firecracker!
Really nice.
A crank!
Crank it up!
So, okay.
Let's think about this.
There looks to be some kind of power power up above the platform.
Just like Super Mario.
I can't jump to that, but I jump on this platform, then I jump to the right, and I go the ladder, right?
That seems to be the way.
Okay, go.
Yeah.
This seems good.
Look at that lamp.
Oh.
Little fireflies.
What are these yellow ones?
In the air.
Oh!
We got a little bunny up there.
Hey, buddy!
Oh.
I didn't mean...
I didn't mean to...
Can I interact with you?
Maybe this is the bunny kingdom.
Oh.
Let's grab one more.
Can I read about them?
Oh.
Yeah.
Look at this.
Unlit candle.
There we go!
No?
Okay.
Hmm.
I guess we need a, uh...
A fire thingy that turns things on.
A.K.A.
me.
I'm not sure how to do that.
Can I go right?
Oh!
Of course.
What's this?
Found a map!
Yes!
Uh.
I'm pressing the button.
Oh!
Okay.
There we go.
Oh!
Nice.
This is gonna be so helpful.
Okay.
So that's an enemy.
That's me.
What am I even?
I look like some kind of enemy from Super Mario.
Obviously something's going on down.
Oh!
Something is burning over there.
It's a flame.
Is that the flame I lost?
In the beginning of the game, there were four flames.
And one of them was extinguished.
But that could also just be my HP.
I'm not sure.
Um.
Oh!
I can zoom.
Cool.
What else can I do on the map?
That seems to be it for now.
Guess I'm going up!
Oh, I'm so happy there's a map.
I cannot tell you how happy I am about that.
Oh my god.
I love this music.
We've got a turtle on the left.
A cat.
Is that a lizard?
And then a...
Poppycock?
I'm not sure.
The one on the right.
No, a stork, right?
A stork?
The one with the slender neck.
And they're all sort of on pillars.
Almost like they're revered.
In this kingdom.
I'm assuming it's a kingdom.
Oh!
Didn't mean to do that!
Dang it.
Oh my god.
I love that effect with the smoke.
Really beautiful.
Oh!
That's a quacky!
What's up, quacky?
I don't want to scare you.
Can I pet you?
I don't want to throw a firecracker at you accidentally here.
Maybe I should.
Can I do something with that?
Oh!
Look at the way.
I can swing it across, like, quite a bit.
I'm going to climb up here.
Let's see the map.
Or maybe I start with one level at a time.
No, no, no.
I'm going to climb up.
Climbing up!
That is a Paraguay, I think.
Up there?
No, parrot.
What are they called?
The ones, you know, with the long beak.
Uh, these are gophers.
How do I get up there?
It doesn't even look like it's possible.
God, look at this level here.
How would this even look without the scan lines?
It wouldn't even work, would it?
This is so good.
Oh!
Wait, what?
It's...
I thought me hitting the lamp turned this on, but it's me hitting the button.
Ah, I see.
Uh, so was it...
Was it an open?
One of two.
But it looks like...
I need to stay on it.
Oh, that's a pretty effect, though.
Bounce that lamp.
That is an iguana.
A huge one.
Hello?
Are you a statue?
What is that?
One of those, uh, sticky...
Uh, animals.
Okay, those are not good for me.
Oh, shit.
Someone's behind me.
Okay, we actually have enemies.
I mean, other than the one that tried to kill us before.
Jump!
Guess I'm going here.
I'm gonna get so lost!
Even with the map.
What was that?
Who is that?
Oh.
I see you.
Okay, so I reveal the map, and then I can still see it.
Are you friendly?
Hello!
Follow me, I guess?
We're going on a trip.
Oh, he's a thick boy.
Can you climb?
Come on.
I'm not sure what's going on here.
Oh, can I jump on you?
Oh!
Found a key!
Hell yeah!
Okay, so we have an egg, and a key, and a map.
Gotcha.
Maybe I can use you for something else.
Very interesting little area here.
Are those stalactites?
Or banners?
I think they're banners.
Wait.
Eat fruit?
Oh, okay.
So that is HP.
Confirmed.
Oh, I can eat that too.
That was also a fruit.
I see.
Easy.
I mean, I'm a master.
This is no problem for me.
Unlock door.
Cool.
Whoa!
What?
Where did he go?
Someone ran at me.
And then he was gone.
I guess he jumped up here.
Oh, there's a whole conga line of them now.
My boy's back!
Brian!
What's up, Brian?
How did you get up here?
Something with this wall on the right.
Check it out.
The colors are different.
That calls for a firecracker.
Oh!
What's happening?
I just lost 2 HP!
I'm in trouble.
Okay, okay.
See ya.
Alright, that works.
I guess I scared them off.
But then I accidentally ran into them twice.
That was not good.
At least I know now that they subtracted HP from me.
Brian, I need you to get up here.
So I can jump on your head.
Can you do that for me?
Hmm?
Maybe you can get over here and I can jump on your head.
Okay, that may work, actually.
Yeah!
Wait, there's another Brian!
Version 2.0.
We gotta find a, um...
A matchbook or something to turn on the candle that we found.
So this one needs a button.
I see the button.
So I think we're gonna get to the ladder over there.
I see that.
Yeah.
Come here.
Little bird.
I mean, there sure are animals here.
I'm just taking in these areas.
Is that an elephant?
An image of an elephant.
Maybe this is like animal farm.
But instead of on the farm, it's in the well.
Locked.
Okay.
Oh.
Switch.
Oh, I'm gonna make him hit the buttons.
That's so smart.
Yeah!
Fall down.
Oh, you're gonna make the long trek now.
This way.
There you go.
And...
Go.
Yes!
Sick!
That was great!
I like that.
What are these boxes here?
They look like...
Dice.
You know, the ones you throw?
And wish for good luck.
So that opens those.
Okay, that's one button out of two.
I see the other button on the other side.
Wait, how did I...
I think I may have to swing in those lanterns.
No, vines, they're called.
Can I not swing in them?
What happens if I...
Whoop!
Okay, there's no fall damage.
That's good.
Well, shit.
We gotta get back up.
Maybe I can do it without scaring these guys off.
Come here, Brian.
Now we wait.
Come on.
No!
I had one job.
Brian, come here!
Do they hit me while I'm...
Oh, that's good.
Very good.
Worth it for that knowledge.
Shit, we're actually at one HP.
This is problematic.
Oh, I can...
I can jump on these?
Say what?
I didn't even know.
So, did we go left or up?
Oh, questions, questions.
I think I'm gonna go left and try and click on that yellow button.
Do I see food?
Is this food?
It's not food.
Brian is back.
See, I wonder...
Can I get through this somehow?
I'm holding down while jumping.
Usually that takes you through a platform in 2D games.
Not here, though, it seems.
But I guess...
Oh, yeah.
I can walk here.
Oh.
Can I make Brian come over here?
Scare him.
Oh, he's so scared.
I'm sorry, Brian.
Maybe I scare him up here.
Sorry.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Yes, Brian.
You did it.
Oh.
That drops a chest.
But...
Oh, no.
I needed him to not fall all the way down, I think.
Unless I can...
Hmm.
Oh, no.
Even if he was here, I couldn't jump on him because the button needs to be pressed.
So, how do I get up there?
Brian?
Can I destroy this with firecrackers?
I have none left.
Crap.
Okay, we gotta go back.
Locked.
Okay.
Firecracker me.
Or maybe I go up here and see what's going on.
Just to have a...
peek, you know?
That's a telephone!
You know what?
I...
Is that food I can eat?
It's not.
Okay.
Um...
Fine, I'll save.
Why do we have all these gophers here?
Go for a kingdom.
They're so cute!
I love these animals.
So wait, there's actually nothing here.
Push the lamp.
Oh, there we go!
That's a fruit.
They're really hard to see.
There's another one!
Oh, shit!
I see them now.
They're hidden behind the grass.
Oh, oh!
We got a secret!
Oh, that is so well hidden, too!
I really gotta be on the lookout.
So if I open the map now...
That shows up now.
Great.
Okay.
Very cool.
Now I wanna save the game again.
Is that crazy?
Just because I got the healing.
Yeah.
I'm not seeing anything else here.
Let's look for those little openings.
Any more...
Oh!
So he's back up there now.
We got one firecracker.
Can I make him come to me?
If I jump up here, he should be coming, right?
Go quick!
Oh, you bastard!
Uh...
Okay, stay there!
Stay there!
Don't move.
Wait, that's not gonna help me, is it?
If I walk over here, he's gonna come towards me, no?
So that drops a chest down there.
Oh, maybe I have to make him push the chest.
I think I see the stance here.
I think I get it.
Brian is the pusher.
He is the supplier.
So, basically,
we do that first.
And now we wanna bring him to this side?
Come here!
Oh!
No, I didn't need you to do that.
I need you to push it to the right, if it's possible.
Oh, shit.
So the chest falls down, and it's right next to this block beneath it.
That means there's no way to actually push that chest with this guy.
So I think I have to get up there.
Unless we push the chest down and use that chest on a button, somehow, but that still needs him pushing the chest to begin with.
Let's go back in.
So this is the initial state.
I can make him walk to the left and right at my will.
Oh!
I have an idea.
Check this out.
We're gonna make him walk to the left first.
Come here, Brian.
Stand there.
There.
Yeah!
I'm sorry, Brian, if it hurt your head.
This way.
A little bit more.
There.
A little bit.
Oh, he drops it.
Oh, because I see he barely fits there.
That's cool.
Very good.
Found a key.
Cool.
Can I push this chest on the button now?
It doesn't seem like it.
But that's cool.
We got the key.
Very cool.
That's a nice puzzle.
Made me feel smart.
And that's that.
Now those doors are gone.
We can make our way back.
This is great, man.
I'm loving this.
This is good fun.
Okay, so we can jump down.
And that is open now.
Oh, my God.
That's beautiful.
And Brian is here waiting for me.
It's fantastic.
Also, we have an animal on the right there.
You see that?
Oh, never mind.
I thought it was an animal with, like, moving feet.
His feet were vibrating.
But it's...
What is this...
I can't figure out the color.
Red lamp.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
I don't have any firecrackers.
I have one.
Oh, there was one there.
I missed it.
Okay, we made it.
Brian, I need you to come over here.
That's a massive animal!
Iguana alert!
I think he's...
He's evil.
He wants me.
That's two buttons.
We need one more.
It's up there.
I see.
But his tongue is gonna be on me.
Oh, no!
What is he...
Okay.
You do you, buddy.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Interesting sounds.
If I jump up and hit you, will I die?
Oh, no.
He's...
Spitting on me now.
Oh!
Did I get hit?
Jump!
Don't tongue me!
Okay, we're good.
Not bad.
Why is he angry with me?
Oh!
Oh, he ate it!
The tongue grabbed it?
That's cool.
Alright, we made it.
Uh, what's this?
Fruit.
Yes, four out of four.
I will not die a single time in this game, by the way.
Because I've played Hollow Knight, okay?
I am pretty, uh, you know...
Experienced with platforming.
I'm pretty good at this stuff.
Oh, it's just a straight-up ladder.
Gotcha.
Oh, dude.
Levels are beautiful.
This may be my favorite art style of any 2D game I've played already.
I am just that much of a sucker for...
Retro effects like this.
Excuse me?
A slink?
Can I not read about them or something?
Maybe it's not that type of game.
Aha!
Oh, that's amazing!
And I pick it up again!
Oh, shit!
Oh, you need to stay on it.
I see.
Oh!
I see what's happening here.
Check it out.
Oh.
I gotta stand here.
Yeah, there we go.
Now I get ready.
But what about my...
Okay, so it stays in place.
Good!
Now I go grab that.
Take it with me.
There's also stuff down here.
Well, well, well.
Uh...
I didn't even intend to make that joke.
Whoopsie-daisy!
Okay.
We fell all the way down.
Where are we right now?
We got more flames!
Uno, dos, tres!
What's this?
Right.
Um, where am I going now?
What's this?
Opens one of them.
Doesn't stay down.
So we need to slinky this, I think.
Does the slinky go through the binky?
It does!
Oh!
Oh, it's back!
Okay.
I thought I lost it forever.
Jump!
We made it.
So I guess when the slinky falls in water, it is returned to me.
That makes sense, because when I fall in water, I'm returned to me.
Yeah!
Okay, man, I'm killing it.
Those are kangaroos!
And a bear.
And then we have a, uh...
A parakeet up here.
Oh, you mad?
Oh!
Oh, sh- Oh!
No!
Firecrack!
Crack my fire!
How do I switch items?
Crack it!
Get scared, get scared!
Oh, okay.
So I can reset them by going back.
That's a universal rule.
Why did I anger him?
So I don't want to go up there.
Oh!
Okay, that's scary as hell, actually.
I don't like that.
Um...
I guess I can't climb the ladder, then, because he's gonna go grab me.
That bastard.
We need, um, to scare him with the firecrackers, for sure.
Oh, there's one.
Question is, how do I do this?
Where do I throw it?
Hey, buddy!
He's not scared of it!
Oh, we made it.
Okay.
Maybe I didn't need firecrackers.
Those are animals!
Or human heads, in the water!
Why?
Okay, that...
Yeah.
Fuck.
I didn't mean to jump in twice.
Yeah, we're in grave danger now.
I wonder if these things that are falling from the...
sky...
are gonna hurt me.
I'm not gonna risk it, not with one HP.
Okay, I can't make it up there.
Okay, it's not gonna hurt me.
Good.
That's not gonna work either.
Jump!
So far, so good.
This lamp is blue.
Bonk it.
Bonk the lamp.
Actually, I wanna make it across.
Ooh, I didn't even see those guys!
In the atmosphere.
Thank you!
If I jump here, I will take damage.
I figured it out.
Up or left?
Let's go...
Yeah, let's go up.
That makes more sense here.
Huh.
There's like a temporary platform razor.
Oh god, how am I gonna do this without taking damage?
Haha!
They tried to bait me in that one!
Think I'm falling for that?
No, sir!
Oh!
Hahaha!
Okay.
Um...
That's the platform.
I'm not falling for your tricks!
Oh.
Yep!
We made it.
I got no firecrackers left.
I wonder if the slinky can do me any favors.
Can I s... Oh, I can switch.
Oh, that's smart.
Okay, much better.
Oh, wait a minute.
Check this out.
That's cool.
I love this.
What a great concept.
Slinky?
Whoa, whoa.
We've got a little something here.
What's the point of this?
Oh, to get up here, I guess?
Okay.
Uh-oh, we're going to jail.
Blocked.
And it looks like that is a button that we need for that.
Question is, which button and where is it?
Maybe it's not even on this screen.
It's not here.
Look for little openings in the pixels.
Maybe here.
Oh.
Something going to happen?
No?
Hmm.
Oh, maybe I slinky that.
Oh.
That's so good.
Cool.
Very good.
God, what a... what a nice concept.
The slinky, huh?
Telephone!
Yes.
Save my progress.
I've made... no, actually, we should eat this first and then save.
What is that?
What even are those things in the ceiling?
Loving.
Loving the particle effects.
It's almost like a little...
Oh, look, you can illuminate the little people when you get closer.
I just realized how that works.
Lovely particle effects.
What's this?
Uh-huh.
Wait, does that mean I can...
Wait, wait, wait.
Uh, come on.
Throw...
No?
Okay, I thought maybe I could go upstairs with it because it, you know, raises the platform.
That is a bird.
Oh.
Are you gonna be aggressive?
Aggressive bird.
Dude, this map is massive already and...
I even missed the path over here on the left.
And here.
Also here.
Actually, many, many places.
I hope I can get some kind of legend on this map that will tell me...
things.
Because right now it's a little hard to keep track of.
This looks like a slinky situation.
Can I make that jump?
What is that in the back?
Little cubby hidey holes?
Look at that little castle or something.
Who made that?
Oh!
There is a bear on the left and he looks to be angry.
His eyes are open.
Maybe you would like a firecracker.
Oh, I don't have any.
Hmm.
Well, I know what to do.
I think.
I gotta get over here.
This doesn't look to be possible.
What is this?
Takes me up there.
Ah!
Of course.
This is so funny.
Oh, but that doesn't do anything for me.
Blocked.
Huh.
Okay.
Can I do anything with you?
Slinky time.
No?
I'm gonna go over here then.
Explore this little region.
One, two, three...
Four, five, six.
Six sided...
Dice.
Or everywhere.
Doesn't look like there's an access...
To this.
Where could I enter?
Is there a path over here?
Maybe a little pipe or something.
Slug cat style.
Doesn't look like it.
By the way, I haven't died at all.
A bear man.
Are you going to be...
Angry?
Oh, you're throwing rocks?
Found chaos egg.
Oh!
Ah, that hurts!
Stop!
Asshole!
I'm not gonna go that way again.
What a bastard.
I wonder what happens if I throw firecrackers at him.
Maybe scare him a little bit.
So, what am I supposed to do with these eggs?
I have two of them now.
I have the map and I also have some kind of line down there.
I don't know what that is.
Oh, maybe it's just a divider in the menu.
That could be it.
Oh, wait a minute.
I just realized.
Slinkies can go through the floor here.
Switch.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah!
But how do I...
Uh-oh.
Retrieve me.
Oh, okay!
So, oh, I see.
So I can retrieve it at will.
That's nice.
Okay, okay, okay.
I need you to go right, though.
Can you do that for me?
Maybe over here?
Eh, not quite.
This one's gonna take me...
Eh, that works, I think.
Ha-ha!
Okay.
And now to get to the other one, we gotta do it here.
And then have it turn right, if we can.
Ah!
The platform's gonna raise it to the left, I see.
So in that case...
How are we gonna get it in there?
Maybe I can...
...mess with it?
No?
Hmm.
Yeah, how do I make it turn?
If I face right...
It's still gonna go left.
Why is it going left?
What determines that?
If I put it here...
That's always gonna go left if it hits that platform.
I guess the only way to do this is to get it on the right side.
And then it's gonna find its way all the way to the bottom right.
The question is how.
Not that way.
Oh!
No!
Ah, there we go!
Okay, okay.
I feel like I tried this one, though.
Why did...
Oh!
Oh, so it is the way you're facing.
Confirmed.
Okay.
I understand now.
So if you're facing right...
The initial...
Direction will be right as well.
Cool.
Oh, those are...
Those are bad guys!
Hold on.
I can probably jump up here.
That looks to be...
Friendly.
Mind if I just...
Ah-ha!
Good luck.
Have fun.
Very good.
Shadow egg.
Looks like a little poop emoji, doesn't it?
Just a little bit?
I'm sensing secrets here, by the way.
Secret sensor 4000 is tingling so much right now.
Ah.
Okay.
Oh.
What do you- Ooh!
Right.
Did I miss some food down here?
Doesn't look like it.
Ah, but wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa whoa whoa, whoa hold on a minute.
What's this?
Oh.
Oh right, I was here before.
Ah, but there's food.
Thanks.
Wait, do I see more food?
No, that's a chest.
Thanks, buddy.
Wait, if I go back in, the food back?
No.
Okay.
Trying to see if I can, you know, clever use of game mechanics here.
Didn't look like I could.
Okay, we're running.
Please don't... Wait, what?
I didn't mean to do that.
Okay, they were not angry.
Oh, this is gonna be bad.
Um, okay, so there's two yellow buttons, which is gonna activate the door.
There's a red button.
That I assume is gonna be bad if I press.
So I think I'm just gonna... Okay!
Wow, how come they're not reacting to me?
I'm kind of curious, though, now.
Nah.
Nah!
Slinky?
Ooh!
They didn't like that at all!
Amazing.
Okay.
We're gonna first try this one now.
You ready?
My aim is the right button... bottom right.
All right?
So.
This one.
Nailed it.
Okay.
My aim is the bottom... left from the most right.
You ready?
Oh wait, that's not gonna... Shit!
I fucked up!
Hold on.
We can do this.
There, there, yeah.
This one.
Nailed it.
Okay, good.
We don't wanna hit the red one, otherwise they're gonna get angry.
Oh, they...
Careful now.
Careful.
Let me think about this.
So here, here...
That's bad.
If I do here...
I guess if it reaches a corner, it's gonna turn around and the new direction is determined.
So I think it's actually this one.
Please be right.
Yeah, dude.
Bonk that lamp!
Victory bonk!
Okay, now.
Now I'm up here.
Oh, of course.
Press the button.
And then we have access...
I didn't pay attention.
Watch is opened.
I guess it's a little, um...
Flapjack over here.
Nope.
Oh, this door!
Okay, I see, I see.
I gotcha.
But what about the top part?
Surely I can get up there.
That still requires a button.
Presumably this button here in the bottom right.
But how do I open this door, then, is the question.
Hmm.
That's a tricky one.
Not sure.
Dude, I...
This is great!
I'm loving this game so far.
Good shit.
Okay, we got an X.
We got two lines.
Two lines, uh, rotated 90 degrees and a square.
And they correspond to the buttons this guy is walking on.
Gotcha.
Easy.
What happens if I do this?
No, Slinky, come on.
Go on adventures.
Okay, you're not gonna go on any adventures.
That's fine.
I can do that myself.
Oh, I should...
I've probably just gone immediately.
Bup!
Uh-oh.
Can I even...
Okay, I can reach.
Go!
This is so funny.
Here.
Uh.
Don't get squashed.
Nice!
Give me my slinky back.
Um.
Is that a dolphin on the right?
Looks like a statue of a dolphin.
How do I get there?
Jump!
I can't reach.
Shit.
Are you gonna be...
Oh!
Eat fruit.
Nice!
4 HP.
So, buddy, are you gonna wake up or...
What's happening here?
What's the dealio?
Okay.
So, this button's gonna activate the square above me.
And we have a...
Another box of a...
Oh.
I know what to do.
I figured it out already.
But!
I need to think first.
About something else.
Unrelated to the current puzzle.
I'm thinking about the laundry right now.
In my real life.
Like, did I actually do it or not?
You know?
Let me just consider that for a moment.
Um.
So, that's gonna go boop, boop, boop, boop.
And then when the boop hits the boop, we go...
That's the square.
That's the two lines.
Then we have, uh, the...
Thingy.
And that's gonna go up, I presume?
That's gonna go...
Whoop!
And then we go down.
And then we're gonna go...
Oh, I see.
Okay.
You ready?
Here we go.
Oh, wait.
Shit.
No!
I almost did it!
I shouldn't have gone down!
Whoops!
Try again.
No!
I should have jumped!
Ah!
Oh, my God.
You gotta be fast.
Okay.
It's a little tough.
I'll admit that.
Yes!
Go!
Oh!
That was close!
Okay, we can also go to the right here.
Oh!
Watch your luck at that!
But, before we do, I can see that this leads back to, uh...
Also, there's also a waterfall on the right.
This leads back up where we were before.
I saw that on the map.
Bonk that lamp.
Open that.
And now, we're gonna go up here.
Boop!
Why is that bear so angry, though?
Oh, we got little people down there.
Is this gonna aggravate them?
Let's see.
No!
They're okay with that.
What did that just do?
I didn't pay attention.
Uh, once more.
It pressed a button with the X on it.
Oh, I see, I see.
I think I see.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Gotcha.
I see what's going on here.
So I click this, and we go up fast.
Go.
Yes, that's so cool.
What a fantastic idea with the slinky.
I've never seen anything like that.
Very cool.
So, this is gonna kill me, no?
Oh, no, that opened the door.
I see.
Bonk the lamp.
I'm looking for fruits, but I don't need them, actually.
Match!
I know what to use that on.
Where was it?
If it's not indicated by a marker, I will never find it again.
Never.
Oh, wait, it was a...
Was it down here?
It was very beginning, wasn't it?
It was in the very beginning.
Um, okay.
Now.
What's next?
Bonk the lamps.
There's a button down below.
I can press on that.
Yeah, okay.
Permanent button.
Oh, no, it's not.
Never mind.
Oh, right.
I see.
Oh, you gotta be fast.
Ah-ha, I see.
Smart.
Wait, what?
Oh, I see the problem.
Huh.
Right.
Well, well, well.
Ain't that a conundrum.
There's some bonking.
I see firecracker.
Oh, is that gonna take me back to the start?
There's no fall damage, right?
So, we're good?
Wee!
Oh, my God.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yeah.
We're all the way back here now.
Maybe this is the spot with the match.
What's up, quacky?
Oh!
Oh, my God.
It's the cat from the picture.
From the thumbnail I did.
I guess that's where that comes from.
That is...
Wait, is that a bunny or a cat?
I'm not sure what that is, actually.
Also, it's like a, um...
Old-school pixel board thingy.
What's going on with that?
Oh, look at them.
They're in love.
Holy matrimony?
The altar of marriage?
It's blocked.
Oh.
Wait, wait, wait.
Before I go this way...
I gotta find the...
The lamp I could turn on.
With the match.
It wasn't here.
Also, I can go down.
I'm not gonna do that yet.
I'm scared of down.
Let's climb up here instead.
It must be...
Oh, is that the one?
I think I see it.
It's the one right above me, right?
No, how do I get there?
That's not the one.
Maybe it is...
It's gonna be a problem, isn't it?
Ah!
Fuck!
Okay, he's angry now.
Jesus!
Let him eat the firecracker!
Come on, eat the firecracker!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh!
I thought he would eat the firecracker and then blow it up in his mouth!
That sounded wrong.
But you know what I mean.
Shit.
Where's the...
I will never find this lamp again.
I will never find this lamp.
Maybe I do just continue here.
Let's see.
We can also go save the game over here.
And then go left.
Let's try that!
We never tried that, did we?
I see the phone!
I always think it looks like one of those TNT detonators.
Save it.
Oh my god, it's the bird people.
Fruit.
Can I not store fruit in my mouth?
You know, like those rodents?
For a rainy day or something.
Take a shower.
My character's so cute!
I just want to squish it!
You know, put my hand on it and go boop boop boop.
That's a massive egg!
I think.
Uh...
The bird has an antenna on its head.
Yes, yes, connection established.
Found stamps!
For my stamp collection?
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, cool!
Okay.
So, a legend.
Oh no, this is...
Oh, I see now.
I see now.
Okay.
I understand.
So, we can put markers.
Zero, I don't...
Zero out of 64.
Okay.
Is that my progression?
Oh, these are the eggs I found!
That's a peacock up there, by the way.
We gotta let him fly!
So, I guess that's what's happening.
This is like, uh, the mother hen.
Of this kingdom.
And she lost all her eggs.
So, we gotta go retrieve them.
That's what's happening.
Oh!
And when we reach a certain egg threshold, these doors will open.
Cool!
I see now.
Very cool.
The egg room.
Gotcha.
Well, that's nice.
Now we can try and look for, uh...
The light we can turn on.
Oh, never mind.
Let's go up here.
That's a hologram of a fox.
Also blocked.
Oh, man.
I love this style.
Of graphics.
It's incredible.
Oh, I thought that was a secret.
I bet you there's a million secrets in this game.
It's a dog!
Are you gonna be angry?
Hello?
Yeah!
Is that good or bad?
I don't know.
Maybe he's a good doggo.
I guess I'll just jump over you?
Jump!
Oh!
Okay, it's bad.
It's bad for me.
Shit.
Okay.
Uh, can I interest you in a slinky?
Play with that.
You don't like the slinky!
No!
Okay.
Um, this is not good.
I'm gonna go down and grab that food I saw.
I saw food.
Somewhere.
Wait, switch?
Oh!
Didn't even see that.
Hold on.
I need food, though.
Wait, where am I now?
Oh, this is new.
This is a new spot.
That is a rabbit.
What is that?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Take disc.
Oh, God.
This is not good.
Oh, my God.
Oh,
my God.
Buttons!
Where's the buttons?
Oh, no.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, that's horrible.
I hate...
Oh, my God.
He's following me.
Just stay away, please.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
He's still coming.
I'm fucked.
It's over.
See you, bitch.
No!
Mistakes were made!
I had one job.
Fuck!
I didn't die, right?
Did I die?
I may have died.
Shit.
Oh, well, first death doesn't count.
We all know that.
It doesn't count.
I don't know if I want to go there again.
Man, that was honestly...
Extremely creepy.
Shit.
That's a fish!
On a pill- It's posing!
Ready for the close-up.
Wait, I feel like I'm going the same direction I went before, and I always end up in a new area.
Okay, we've got a switch.
And we have a chest.
So I can't reach that like this.
I can't reach it like this either.
Maybe one thing at a time here.
I'm getting hella distracted.
I don't want to go back to that fucking creature.
I never want to go back to that creature.
But maybe I have to.
Okay, this is the way.
No, it's not.
It's not.
Is it up here?
Yeah, this is it.
Oh, God.
Oh, wait a sec.
What do we have here?
Okay, thank God you cannot die from fall damage.
I have trouble seeing what is, um, standable platforms, and which ones are transparent.
Wait, that's not the way I went.
I'm going to go up here.
We're going to try this now.
Oh, I see.
I see now.
Okay, okay.
So this I can stand on.
This I can stand on.
What if I slinky here?
Is I going to hit a button down below somewhere?
Wouldn't that be cool?
Oh, I see a switch.
Oh, I think I get it.
So we have to flip this switch?
And then something will have changed in here.
Oh, never mind.
That closes the door.
I see.
Okay.
Then I don't understand.
How on earth am I going to get over there?
Can I slinky?
Nope.
I guess I'll be back.
Because this, uh, thing here I can't stand on.
Ah, maybe I slinky?
Can I slinky the lever?
No.
Okay.
Fah!
I'm going to take a quick break.
And then I'm going to try and get around the creature on the left.
I'll see you guys in like five minutes.
Hey, guys.
So apparently there's an option in the settings.
That I should turn off.
Or on.
Which is reduce flashing.
I can do that.
There is a bit of flashing for sure when you throw the firecrackers.
Reduce flashing.
There we go.
Done.
What?
What happened?
I didn't do anything.
That's a scary sound to hear when you didn't do anything.
Hopefully everything's working.
It seems to be working.
Anyway.
Guys.
How is the sound now?
Now that we've been playing for a little bit.
Is it okay?
The sound levels?
There was a bit of concern with it earlier.
The music.
The effects.
And my voice.
Is it all balanced well?
Yeah?
Okay.
Great.
Can you see how the game looks like without scan lines?
Yes.
Also, I'm going to start playing again.
Let's take a look what it looks like without.
Okay.
It doesn't look that bad, actually.
But I definitely prefer it with on.
Yeah.
For sure.
I mean, I like the scan lines.
This is...
It really adds something.
In my opinion.
Look at my character sleeping.
Dreaming of bunnies jumping.
Or running.
That's cute.
So, I guess my character really, really loves bunnies.
I'm a bunny man.
Okay.
So, hold on a second.
I don't want to do this, then.
I don't want to take the disc.
Because then this creature is going to go crazy.
Maybe I'll scout my way ahead here first.
Okay.
So, that's going to lower...
Raise that.
Okay.
So, I jump up there.
I jump on that.
Then the button.
Yes.
Go.
Good.
And then we go...
Whoa, whoa.
So, I guess I need the disc.
If I do this...
Go in the next, uh...
Area.
Whoops.
I wonder if that is persistent.
It is.
Okay.
Thanks.
See you, nerd.
Bye-bye.
Oh, my God.
You're fast.
You move through walls.
No answer.
I need help.
Do you come in?
Oh, we have a problem.
Okay.
I can return the disc.
That's nice.
That's good to know.
Um, I may just take another look here.
I don't know why I'm doing that.
Maybe I can crush the creature.
Now I can see...
Okay.
You can't save when the thing is after you.
Okay, so if I go right, we need a...
I see.
We gotta push a button for that one.
I guess I'll not grab the disc yet.
I will save the game.
And we will jump on this platform.
Cross our fingers.
Scrub our toes.
Moisturize our body.
And get ready.
Yoink!
Where am I?
Oh, it's a doggo.
Hey, doggo, do you like slinkies?
Eh?
No?
You don't like them?
What am I supposed to do here?
He's gonna come running at me and bite me.
And it's going to be...
A disaster.
Oh, I see.
You can't follow me, can you?
Yeah!
You too big?
Only small ones like me can fit.
I kind of want to pet the dog still.
It's just part of my natural instincts.
Okay.
Is the game telling me I may need these now?
Oh, this is...
Very dark.
Okay.
Those are spikes!
Up again.
Okay, so this is where I came from.
There's nothing else.
I can't go down here, it seems.
I guess I can test the...
Oh!
I can fall down there somehow.
Oh.
Ooh!
What?
Oh, I thought there were spikes!
They look like spikes to me.
What?
But...
Oh!
Bro, it is way too dark in here.
I need a lamp!
Can I use the candle?
The match?
My one match?
Can I...
Probably not.
Oh!
Found a secret, I think.
It's a fern.
I'm so scared.
Oh, now I'm back here.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
I guess we gotta go along the spikes.
Somehow.
Those are just spikes.
There's nothing else there.
Oof.
Oh, this is making me tense.
The darkness is not good for my sanity.
Okay, that's good.
I guess they serve as a good light source.
Let me...
Okay.
Very good.
Oh, no.
Hey!
That's what I'm talking about!
Get flashbanged.
I saw a food down here.
Nope, that's a firecracker.
Wait, is he about to respawn?
Please don't respawn.
There's definitely some kind of animation happening up there.
Maybe after, like, ten blimps, he's gonna appear again.
Okay.
Maybe take another look.
No, I have one firecracker left.
I gotta save it.
I see the light at the end of the tunnel.
Let's throw a firecracker.
Okay.
Thank you.
We gotta raise this.
Easy.
But you know what?
I'm not satisfied yet.
I'm going for the crazy play here.
You'll see what I mean.
Oh, wait.
No, I can't.
Oh, okay.
Fine.
No, hold on.
I'm going for the crazy play.
No!
It's all the way down now.
Okay, I can't go back.
Shit.
I hear a dog.
Oh, God.
We're back here.
Okay.
Wait, this is not the same place, is it?
This is a different dog.
This is Benny.
Hey, Benny.
Do you like firecrackers?
Check that out.
Oh, you get scared!
Okay.
Huge.
But wait, he's all the way over there now, so he's not going to make it here in time.
Haha!
Okay, I thought he could jump up here.
We're safe.
Where am I?
Good.
I hear all kinds of animal sounds in the distance.
Oh, God.
That opens the top one there.
There's another lever.
I know what to do.
Oh!
Shit!
Oh, no.
Doggo!
Hey, come here!
Dumbass!
Now I go the other way.
Outsmarted, outplayed.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Secret?
I thought I could go to the right there.
Okay.
But what's the dealio here?
Cool!
But!
It also looks like there's paths to the west.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Yeah, there is!
Look!
How would you do that?
So, you've got to end up on the top left platform.
Can I even make that jump, though?
Even if I was there?
Looks unlikely.
I'm going to go this way.
I'm scared.
Okay.
Doggo statues.
There's that doggo from before.
So intricate!
This is like a highway back home.
Did I miss anything in this place?
The map is a little hard to read.
What is...
Oh, I thought it was a pillar I could stand on.
Mock disc?
Oh, I see what we're going to do.
We're going to pull an Indiana Jones.
I've never actually seen Indiana Jones, but I know that's what he does.
How am I going to get in there?
Shit.
That button right there needs to be pushed real bad.
And I need to do it.
Are those mice on the pillars?
I'm not sure what they are.
Okay, doggo.
Can you be good to me?
How am I going to do this?
Hey.
Wait, maybe you're a good doggo.
You're brown.
Different color.
Maybe different breed.
Maybe different temper.
There's also stuff up here.
Okay, you can't reach me.
Whoa!
Shit!
Oh, fair!
Oh my god!
Wow!
Fuck, that caught me off guard.
Jesus Christ.
He was way faster than me too.
I couldn't outrun him.
I'm not sure when I saved.
Do I still have my...
I have the mock disc.
Oh no, I don't like that at all.
Hey, come here.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's a brown dog.
It's one of those that like to dig, right?
I forgot the name of the...
Grave robber or something.
Gravehound?
Something like that.
Okay, let's make our way through this again.
Duh!
Okay, we're good.
Wait, no, no.
This is the wrong way.
Wrong way.
No, it's not.
It's not.
It's correct.
Grab that.
Okay, you want a piece of this, right?
That's not the piece I was gonna give you.
Let's try that again.
Get scared, nerd.
Wait, something's glowing up here.
Whoa, wait a minute.
That's so nice.
Look at those colors.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Oh, man.
That brings me so much happiness.
I gotta light all the candles.
Right, this was this thing.
Okay, I'm gonna go for the play this time.
Check it out.
Fuck!
Ah, never mind.
Is there even anything up there?
Probably not, right?
Okay, doggo.
Come here.
Oh, he didn't even see me jump up.
That's funny.
He still thinks I'm down there.
So sneaky.
Why did I not make that jump?
Because I'm not good enough, is the answer.
No more messing around.
Frame perfect jumps now.
Wait, not that way.
If I jump at the same time I press...
Oh!
Can I do it mid-air?
No.
Doesn't look like it.
There's something above me, though.
Look.
There's a little something-something there.
How would I do this?
You know what?
I should put a marker.
Fuck yeah.
Let's do...
Question mark.
Here.
Right there.
Something's going on here.
It's marker time.
Okay.
Let's not mess this up now.
I actually forgot what I did.
What happened over here.
I remember this.
Right.
We need to find the button.
So this is the button over here.
Something needs to squeeze through here.
Real tight.
And press that button.
Whoops!
That was the wrong button.
I don't take damage from that, do I?
I don't think so.
Okay.
This was the dog that really messed me up.
I'm gonna have to scare it away.
I'm pretty sure.
No way.
I can't see my character!
Run!
Go, go, go, go!
Go!
Where?
What?
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, I can't, I can't...
No!
I'm not going back there.
I don't understand what the hell the point is of that.
What is the point?
Oh, so that's where I died.
That's the died symbol.
I see.
I don't get the point of that.
There's nowhere to go.
But it looks like I can, uh, access it from the right side.
Maybe I'll try that instead.
Or...
Was that the door that I couldn't open?
Probably, right?
I think it may have been.
Because it's actually right over here.
To my right.
Oh!
Swap the disc!
Okay, so we got a disc now.
What's the point?
Can I...
Oh!
What, it's like a, um, one of, one of those, um...
You know, like, fucking ultimate...
A frisbee!
Like a frisbee.
Okay, so, something interesting.
It looks like the physics simulation is paused when you're not in the screen.
Where you activated it.
So this thing was stuck...
Up here.
Until I arrived back here.
And then it started falling down.
That's a cool observation there.
Maybe I can, uh, shoot the dog now.
It sounds cruel, but...
He's been cruel to me!
That's all I'm saying.
Oh!
Oh, wait.
Oh, it goes back and forth!
Look!
It'd be bouncing!
Oh, that's cool.
Very neat.
Maybe I can shoot the creature with it.
The evil creature of the night.
Oh my god!
That's the third time I missed a platform!
I'm not good at platforming.
I admit it.
It's a fault of mine.
Okay.
Oh my god, I almost missed it again.
Hey, bitch!
Oh, shit!
Oh, okay.
Wait, what?
It wants to play catch!
Shhh!
Oh!
Cool!
Okay, so minor distraction, I guess.
It still doesn't help me, because I don't know what to do when I'm inside those little tunnels.
It's a problem.
It is a big one.
Big problem.
What is that sound?
What's the dick, dick, dick, dick sound?
Okay, we got the firecrackers.
I didn't mean to do that.
Wait, wait, wait!
There was something up there!
Big ball play.
This time I'm doing it.
I can't see anything.
Oh, but wait, it's not gonna go back up, is it?
I'm, I'm the, I'm a dumbass.
I, for some reason, I thought it was gonna go back up afterwards, but that's not the case.
Fine.
I'll be moving on.
Wait, what is going on here?
Oh, that's the doggo, okay.
But, hold on, isn't this a little shortcut, then?
Catch!
Yes!
Good boy!
Good doggo.
Ah.
I was trying to go for the MLG play.
Let me try again.
Ah!
That was sick.
Heh heh heh.
Okay, we got the frisbee.
Look at these statues of dogs.
Like, what is going on?
With these dogs, huh?
Maybe they're just hungry.
Maybe nobody fed them in a while.
Or maybe they just wanna play, you know?
They think I'm a little, uh, chewy toy.
I mean, I kinda look like it.
Right?
I look like one of those toys that go, Wee, wee, when you squeeze them.
Oh, I see!
Oh!
Beautiful!
Wonderful!
Oh, and then I'm back here.
That's nice.
What a shortcut.
In fact, how about we go save the game now?
Let's ring up the people, and let them know where we are.
The status is good.
It's green all across the board.
And we're about to, uh, give this dog a little toy.
Hey, buddy!
Okay, okay, I was just checking.
You do like to play.
Oh, shit.
Catch!
Oh, that's cool!
Can I chain this together?
Oh, I can just keep doing it.
Okay, cool.
Very nice.
And now the shortcut has been unlocked.
God, that's, that's really nice.
Fucking, they nailed this part.
With the progression feeling here.
What, where's the, where's the, I'm gonna, I'm gonna frisbee everything.
Hey, dog!
That's for you!
Can I frisbee the...
Ah-ha!
Look at that!
Ah, ah, that's awesome.
Hup!
Wait, what?
Wait a sec.
Hmm.
Oh, I see, I see.
Check this out.
Oh!
Wait, what?
Okay, you gotta time...
Oh!
Okay, it's a little, it's a little tough.
Oh, shit!
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold on.
Okay.
Give me a moment.
I need to, I need to mentally, you know, lock in here.
Oh my god.
Ah, it, it...
Ah, it's, it's really difficult.
I almost did it.
You can actually time it with the sound cues.
That's what I did at the end.
Cool!
I love it.
What does that do?
Oh, it opens these.
I see.
I see!
So how do I now get up there?
I picked it up mid-air.
That's another doggo.
Shaped like a mermaid.
What?
Why?
There's some weird lore going on here.
With the doggos in the, in the ocean.
Three doggos.
Oh, I see!
I'm an idiot.
I get it.
Wait.
Haha!
Found a match?
Oh!
I was wondering, am I gonna face into the wall and die a gruesome death?
But I guess not.
What's up here?
Oh!
Hey!
Cool.
Oh, this is so weird.
Open the door!
But now I'm stuck here.
Wait.
Can I not walk on that?
No.
Ah, but wait.
There's more in here I didn't get.
Gotta go back.
We're not done.
Oh!
What?
I got him.
Jesus Christ.
Oh!
It's a candle!
What?
Oh, now I'm back up here.
Okay.
I don't want to do that.
There was a chest, no?
Yeah.
There it is.
So I guess I gotta go here.
Okay.
I thought I was taking damage by standing on them, but I guess not.
Whoop.
A depraved egg!
That sounds disgusting.
Uh.
I want to try going left up here now.
Yeah, you can't reach me, buddy.
The thing is, though, here I don't have three frisbees, unfortunately.
Maybe they can play with each other.
Ha ha ha!
They chased us!
That's so funny.
Okay.
Um.
Catch!
Yeah!
Now they can fight about that.
Are those doggos?
I can't tell what this creature is.
I'm actually not very good with animals, like, knowing which animals are which.
I can jump down.
Maybe I want to jump down, yeah.
Oh, no!
Get away from me.
Open that door.
Wait, how am I getting my thing back?
Oh, I guess I shoot it again.
No, wait.
It's stuck there!
Uh-oh.
That's a candle.
Why would I turn it on?
I don't need light in here.
Wait, I can't turn it on.
I have no candles.
Okay.
I mean, matches.
Whatever.
I'm not sure what to do here.
Where can I go?
Jump up here.
Dude, I don't know.
I feel like I'm stuck.
What am I missing?
Something up there, but I can't reach it.
Oh!
You can jump through the thing.
That makes sense.
That makes sense!
It makes sense.
I didn't even see that.
Um, right.
So, I guess that's that.
Now we leave this place.
I'm leaving.
Oh, those are big stalactites!
And guys, remember.
Stalactites, because tits are hanging.
And these are hanging.
That's how you remember it.
Um, if I jump in the water, I'm just gonna get returned here, I think.
What if I slinky the water?
Okay, it's gone.
Right.
Catch it!
Yeah!
Wait.
Yeah.
Huh.
Dude, what if I'm a time traveler right now, and this is actually the past?
Wouldn't that be cool?
But wait, how do I actually proceed?
Okay, you don't want to jump in the water.
Can I shoot up or...
I don't want to shoot up or shoot the lamp or something, but...
Oh, nice.
Very cool.
And now I want to break this for some reason.
Oh, what?
Oh, you take damage when you hit the stalactite.
It makes...
Oh, I gotta grab this thing.
What?!
You can ride the thing!
How badass is that?
That was a complete accident.
I didn't even...
Oh!
Yeah, don't...
Wait, am I going to take damage if I ride it while I'm here?
Oh, that's just gone.
Okay.
No.
Ah, damn it.
Okay.
But I guess that's a good thing?
Oh, wait, no.
I have to do this.
Yes!
Ah-ha!
Sick!
How?
That's actually...
How the hell do you figure that out, like, without accidentally doing it like I just did?
Sounds crazy.
Break that!
Up we go.
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, that's one way, I guess.
Ah, wait, what?
Oh!
Bye-bye!
We don't want your kind here.
I can go up here.
What am I doing?
I'm going to this button down there.
I see.
I'm just gonna...
Okay, I see.
So this one now.
Yep.
Press that.
Opens the door.
Wonderful.
Aha!
Bit of a...
Secret.
Oh, wait.
An upside-down egg.
Isn't that just an egg, though?
If you think about it.
And now I can't get back up.
Oh, now I'm here.
Oh, I think I may know what to do here now!
This opens so many possibilities.
Check this out.
Oh, this is easy.
Uh, here.
Ah, shit.
It's actually kind of difficult to...
Catch.
Oh!
Right, okay.
I'm not very good at jumping on the disc.
Shit.
Eat it, eat it.
I mean, play with it.
I'm totally messing up right now.
My motor skills are lacking.
I admit it.
It's not pretty.
So now...
Now...
This...
Um...
Oh, it's really tough!
Man, you gotta be fast.
This game requires dexterity.
Agility of the fingers.
Switch that.
So, okay.
I do a disc.
Ah!
Watch, watch.
This is so smart.
You ready?
It's gonna come back.
Time it!
Yes!
Baby!
Oh, but wait.
Now I can't...
Yeah!
We made it!
That looks like a skull to me.
But Brian is in there.
It can't be bad then, right?
Brian!
Oh.
Brian, you're kind of in the way right now.
Do you mind?
Okay.
Oh!
Ah!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you, Brian.
Or Brian, the second.
Oh, wait.
I see the problem here.
I see the issue.
Oh, wait, wait.
I know.
Ha ha ha ha!
That is so good.
I'm sorry, Brian.
I needed the red egg, a.k.a.
the tomato.
Dude, this game is fucking good!
Good game.
Let me grab that.
I'm not gonna leave you in...
Oh, look at me!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I love that.
So cool.
The fact that I'm also rotating.
Usually I'm the one who rotates nerds, but now I'm the nerd being rotated.
Um...
Sometimes you just gotta throw the disc and see what happens.
It's...
Okay.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, oh.
I like that sound.
Now we go back here.
I think that was a dead end over there.
Yeah.
Switch that.
Then we go back up.
Oh, but wait, wait, wait.
There's something up there.
See that?
We're not done.
We are not done.
Switch!
Jump!
Okay.
Maybe not.
Unless I do the disc...
Jump?
Disc jump.
Maneuver.
Okay?
Watch.
This is gonna be sick.
Get ready.
Oh, wait.
I gotta wait for the next one.
Up!
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, wait.
I can't reach that.
Damn it.
The strategy was sound, though.
Yeah!
Fuck!
Wait, it's gone forever.
Okay, well.
I'll be back later.
In fact, I'm gonna put a marker.
Oh, that leads back up to where I already was.
I see.
But where was that?
To be precise.
See, that's the question, isn't it?
Now, I want to go back to the burying dog.
The burial dog.
Because there's something going on in those tunnels.
And I want to investigate them.
With my hands.
You know what I mean?
You.
Hold on.
Are those tunnels just a honeypot?
One last look.
Okay.
Really look.
I'm looking.
Can't go down there.
Oh, shit.
He's coming.
Here.
No, wait.
That's just...
Oh, no.
Up!
I see it.
Yeah!
Sour egg in my body!
It's all in there.
All the way.
I'm so glad I did this.
We've got a canine here.
Assault rifles in this...
In this game?
Not coming back.
Okay.
How am I...
Check it out.
Yeah!
Wait, where am I going?
Anyway, the idea was good.
It was a good idea.
I don't know what the plan was, but...
You know.
Ah.
Right.
We found another match!
Very good.
Now, can I please pick this up again?
Oh!
Got it.
Now.
What do I do from here?
We gotta hit the button on the right side.
And to get there, we can also go through this giant pipe.
Or should I say...
Well?
Maybe that's the well.
In the animals.
The kingdom of the animals.
What kind of animal am I?
I don't know.
It's blocked.
Before I adventure here...
Oh, but wait.
How do I even flip this switch back to normal now?
That's a done deal.
We can't.
We gotta go down.
Scaring the birds.
What's with these bird people?
So now I'm back here.
I think it's a good idea to save the game now.
We did some good progress.
Ring up the people.
Let them know that we're safe and healthy.
We arrived.
Now I'm gonna head over here.
It looks like there's a little something-something in the bottom and up here.
Now that we have the disc, we can make all sorts of things happen.
Right.
This place.
Wait, what was the issue before?
Couldn't I have...
Oh, no, I couldn't have.
Okay.
There.
No!
Wait, what am I trying to do?
Why don't I just ride the disc?
Like a normal man.
Yeah, see, now the issue is I gotta grab it again.
I think I'm overthinking this a little bit.
Oh, okay.
It doesn't come back again.
Well, in that case...
That should work.
Yeah.
Wonderful!
The match!
We got it.
Now, to proceed...
Watch this.
No, wait.
That's a bad idea.
Yeah.
Now what?
Okay, that works.
Here.
I'm not sure why I'm going up here, but...
I'm doing it.
Okay.
So if I flip this switch, surely everything's gonna be reversed again.
What's the point of that?
Oh, never mind.
Ah.
What?
Oh, when it hits the vine, it falls down.
Interesting.
I see what's going on here.
Maybe.
Oh, watch.
Oh, smart!
Wow.
It's a virtual egg.
Cool.
All these eggs...
are being found.
And now we're here again.
Oh, look at that little entrance!
Could have just jumped up here at any time.
That is extremely hidden.
Like, look at that.
I could have just gone like this.
Wow.
Okay, so let me take a look at what that looks like.
It's like...
It doesn't even stand out at all.
There's no way I'll find that later.
What is...
Is that a number?
Zero?
Whoa!
We opened the door.
Do I enter?
Oh, great peacock!
You should...
You shall one day fly!
Am I ready?
To face the challenges beyond this door.
No.
Okay.
I'll be back later.
I had other things to do anyway.
Um...
I want to go up here.
Because there's stuff to do.
I don't want to overwhelm myself in the beginning.
With all kinds of areas.
When I can't even find my way around the start.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll take a quick peek, though.
Just...
Just stick my head in there.
Sand in the water.
No, the toe in the water just took...
Nah, nah.
We're gonna...
Nope.
Okay, let's just have a quick look.
There's a chest.
Ooh, okay.
Wait, wait.
So the next level is gonna be a chest.
Bonk the lamp.
Arrange it, bomb.
Bonk.
Ooh.
Uh-oh.
Alarm has gone off.
Brian?
What's happening?
Speak to me.
Oh.
That's not what I wanted to do, but...
I think my...
Intrusion has been...
Locked, you know?
They know about me now.
Can I...
I can jump back up.
Okay.
What is that?
It's just like the bear.
Weird humming sound.
Check out these moves.
Okay.
Check it out, bro.
Wee!
Bra-ba-ba.
Um, maybe I...
No?
You don't care?
What is going on here?
Something's going on with these animals here.
Their lies...
Their eyes light up.
I'm gonna put a stamp.
And I'm gonna call it...
Uh, well, I don't know.
Maybe...
Oh, I...
What is that symbol, even?
Looks like the face of a dog, right?
Can use that.
This is the face of the animals with the lit eyes.
That's the symbol for that now.
Let's go skating.
That's not the skate.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Brian, I need you.
Oh god.
I gotta pick up my disc.
I can't!
I can.
Oh, I can just jump up here.
Haha.
That's easy.
An animal flute!
Okay.
Oh my god.
Look at them coming out of the woodworks.
Wait, what?
Oh, we got dice with multiple...
Look.
Five.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Wait.
Seven.
Eight.
An eight-sided dice.
Or die.
Huh.
I'm shooting little notes.
How neat is that?
Looks like they enjoyed that sound.
Huh, Brian?
Brian is a fan.
What is the deal with it, though?
Like, what is the point?
I guess I can lure animals with it.
Oh yeah, you love it, Brian.
Come here.
That's the song of my people.
Don't forget it.
I want to jump up here.
Watch this.
Wait, how did I do...
I forgot how I did it.
Oh, right.
Okay.
This is so dope.
Oh!
Let me play you the song of my people!
You know where that's from?
Maybe I didn't do it correctly.
Speak to me!
Go inside its mouth.
Whoa.
Oh, I know what this is!
This is a fast travel system.
This is a hub area.
Yes!
I can play the song of my people here.
Ah, I probably have to play it at the butt side, not the face side.
I see.
Yeah.
Wait, there's a bear here too!
Never mind.
This is a different bear.
Okay.
Oh!
You are reacting to me!
Maybe they have their preferred note.
You know?
Maybe the frogs and the fishes, they like high notes and the other ones like low notes.
I don't know.
Dude.
Prediction.
There's going to be a point in this game where I have to play a precise melody and something will happen.
Somewhere.
Also, check out these lights in the background.
Bouncing white lights.
Not sure what's up with that.
Oh, I fucked it up.
That's the song of my people.
Okay, where am I?
Whoa!
I'm way off somewhere else.
Okay.
I got full health.
Everything is rocking.
Oh.
Don't want to jump in the pond.
Oh!
Secret!
Look at that!
But wait.
What about second secret?
I'm not done with secrets.
Yeah, yeah.
Nothing here, huh?
Dude!
What?
Was that a frog?
Just ate my ass.
Ah.
Huh, I see.
Yeah!
Wait, what?
What happened?
What?
Why am I back here?
Did I fuck it up?
I think I did it wrong.
Uh, back down.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, it's actually super easy.
It's just going around in a circle.
Gotcha.
Wait, let me try.
Oh, no, no.
It was...
Oh, I like that sound effect!
Sounds like I did it wrong, though.
It goes...
Wait, let me see that again.
That's exactly what I did.
Oh, I love that sound!
Okay, just, like...
A side note here.
The game is 30 megabytes.
How the fuck is that possible?
Just from the sounds perspective alone.
Sounds take up quite a bit of space.
I guess...
Maybe there's, like, a system of sounds that I'm not familiar with.
Well, I guess there's also a bunch of sounds in Super Mario 64.
How do they do that, right?
I don't know.
People smarter than me figured it out.
Not sure.
So, apparently, when I do that, I get over here again.
Maybe it's, like...
Maybe it's just, like, a fast travel thing.
If you do that, then you're gonna, you know, get here.
Okay.
That's cool.
I guess.
But I'm assuming there's gonna be songs of all the peoples.
My song is this.
Ah, wait.
That's my song.
And when you play that, I will appear behind you.
Uh...
I'm kidding.
Well, that is funny, though.
Um...
Wait!
There's a crocodile man here!
Crocodile man?
Will you do crocodile things to me?
Okay.
Uh...
This is weird.
Why...
Why can't I...
Progress?
Oh?
What just happened?
There.
Slinky on your head.
Enjoy that one, okay?
That's for you.
Just you.
Yeah, yeah.
I...
I understand.
But, watch.
I...
There's another secret here.
Let me show you.
This is what I actually wanted to do before I got distracted here.
Okay, I can't jump on you.
Too bad.
But, maybe I do this.
No!
Hmm.
I wish you would shut up right now.
I'm trying to...
Do something cool here.
Dang.
I pick it up too fast.
Maybe if I arrive from over here.
No?
Oh, okay.
You can't do that.
Never mind.
It's fine.
In fact, you can test for secret passages like this, no?
Like, if I were to stand here and just shoot it.
Yeah, look!
You can test that at long range.
Can't break that.
Alright.
Very cool.
Does it work from anywhere?
Oh!
I can't get enough of that sound!
Oh, it's chocolate in my ears!
And I guess I can just do this now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very cool.
Super mega duper cool.
Okay.
What do I do now, though?
I gotta go through here somehow.
Doesn't look like it's possible.
Unless we can...
So that wakes them up.
Can't break it.
Maybe with this?
No.
I didn't think so.
I'm sorry, Brian.
I didn't mean to scare you.
It's gonna be okay.
You can use it to light up the environment as well.
Very neat.
Well, I guess I'm just gonna move on.
Come back later, perhaps.
I'm gonna put a marker.
Let's do a...
What should be the marker for...
Hey, you can go here, but there's a wall in the way.
Probably this one.
There.
You can go there, but there's a wall in the way.
You gotta do something about that.
Like, check this one out, right?
That one up there can be gotten to from opening the next door, right?
I wanna go find the bear now.
He was over here somewhere.
I think.
He was somewhere off to the right.
Whoops.
Yeah, that's fine.
Kinda wanna try and shoot the birds.
Okay, something I gotta try here.
Hey, quackity quack.
Check what I got.
You don't like that?
Okay, that's fine.
Do you like, uh, to play frisbee?
Okay, you're intrigued by it, but you're not intrigued enough to wanna play with it.
I see your stance.
Is this board reacting in some way?
Doesn't look like it.
You know what?
This is kind of an important place, I think.
We should mark it.
Oh, it's already kind of marked, I guess.
But let's do a marker ourselves.
Nah, I don't wanna saturate the map, either.
Wait, how do I...
No, I wanna clear it.
Oops.
Ah, okay, there we go.
Figured it out.
There's a button there!
Ah, but we can't get in.
Right, I never went here!
I can't shoot them.
Oh!
There's another screen here.
Let's wait with that.
Okay, that's just gonna...
Oh!
That was close.
How am I gonna do this?
Maybe I jump from here.
Oh my god.
Ah!
Shit!
Oh my god.
Okay, that was close.
Ah!
Okay.
So far, so good.
Crap.
Yeah!
Oh my god, I'm so good.
Bonk that lamp.
Wait, wait, wait.
I sense a secret?
No, never mind.
Where's my character?
Oh.
Wait, what?
So this one's already switching back and forth.
Oh, it's the dude up there switching the lever.
I see.
Made it!
But wait a sec.
I have a feeling.
I'm not done here.
Shit!
Okay, never mind.
I thought maybe there was something in the bottom left.
I wanted to illuminate it first.
That's historic!
Okay, he doesn't seem to react to that.
I came from upstairs.
Oh.
Oh!
That scared me.
Oh, that's a light!
Shit!
What the...
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let's do this one.
What the hell just happened?
Why was that so violent?
What is going on here?
What in tarnation?
Look at the way that light bleeds out.
Here, that's a cool effect.
So to get in there, we gotta go...
Where exactly?
I'm not seeing a clear path.
Weird.
Maybe from upstairs?
That's not traversable.
Mark that!
Question mark.
Right there.
Because we don't know what the hell is going on.
We got a bunny man.
On the left.
This is gonna be interesting.
What happens if I...
Throw you some crackers?
They don't care about that?
Ah!
Watch this.
There.
Oh!
Oh, I guess I can just walk.
What am I doing?
I overthought this for sure.
Way too much thinking on that one.
Just...
Just go!
Oh, okay.
Just a bit of healing.
The game was like, You messed up there.
Here.
Let me fix that for you.
But it does look like there's a path down on the left.
I think...
These blocks right here, I'm gonna be able to destroy later somehow.
It's just...
It's gotta be.
What?
It's too dark to see the map.
Oh, okay.
That's a mechanic.
Weird.
So, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna put a potential...
This is me betting on the future.
And me being right.
This is a...
Breakable wall.
Let's make it into this.
That's the breakable wall symbol.
Okay.
There's also something to the left of...
Oh, but how do I get back up?
Oh, my God.
Could I have just...
All this time?
No way.
I didn't even see that.
What the heck, man?
Oh, guess we removed that marker then.
Get rid of that.
No.
No way that was there forever, right?
It wasn't there all the time.
I changed something down there that did this.
I must have.
There's no way I wouldn't have seen that.
These look like hostiles.
See you later, nerds!
All right.
We have a problem.
Oh, that's weird.
Oh, I...
Oh, they're friends!
Okay.
I thought they were gonna hurt me.
Interesting.
Huh.
Well, isn't that a conundrum now?
They look so happy.
All right.
Look at us!
Let me play you the song of my people as we go.
Oh, I can't!
Okay, too bad.
They don't react to that.
Okay.
Now they're all aligned.
Oh, the...
Hmm.
That's a head scratcher.
So that works.
And I can't outrun them, right?
No.
Maybe a slinky will...
That's not a slinky.
There.
Slinky on your head.
I'm sucking out your brain.
Just like starship troopers.
No?
What if I scare you a little bit?
Just a...
A slight scare.
Scare.
Okay, you don't...
You're not faced by that at all.
Gotcha.
Well, well, well.
Nope.
It's something to do with getting them out of alignment here, of course.
How do I get these out of alignment?
Maybe over here?
Now they're sort of misaligned.
But as soon as I jump on it, it's gonna...
It's gonna not work, I guess.
I...
Don't know.
This is...
This is a tough one.
What the heck, man?
What?
How did I just do that?
Is ha...
I don't understand what's happening.
Hold on.
I don't want to progress unless I understand...
No, I...
I don't get it.
What is happening?
Why is he going half invisible here?
What?
Okay, I don't understand it.
I'm just gonna accept it.
He's going half invisible for some reason.
Wait, why did I just do that?
Okay, that opens that.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Oh, so...
Ah!
But isn't that where I came from?
Am I...
What was the point of this room?
Huh?
Oh.
I think that changed something in here.
I don't know what changed.
Didn't I come from here?
No, I didn't.
I...
Okay.
I'm definitely a little lost.
But that's okay.
We're making progress somehow.
Oh, shit.
Oh, sh...
Okay.
We're fine.
Let me play you the song of my people.
I need it to calm me down.
This is the one thing that can calm me.
There we go.
Now.
I may need to ride a disc here.
Boop!
Oh, they...
Okay.
Or...
Wait, why don't I just jump?
Again, I'm overthinking it.
Uh-oh.
Houston, we have a problem.
Actually, that's perfect.
That's what I...
That's what I need.
Oh, shit.
I can't reach.
Oh!
Hmm.
What?
Uh.
Up, up, up, up!
Oh-ho-ho!
Wow.
Misalign!
Huh?
Oh.
I guess that's gonna change something in the other room again.
Fool me once, shame on me.
Fool me twice, shame on me.
Thrice?
No way, Jose.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh!
Except I can't get up there.
Hype!
Okay.
Oh, the vines!
Oh, no.
We can't...
This go way up.
Wait, now I'm fucking...
I can't get back up there.
It's ogre.
It's actually not ogre yet.
Ah, I missed.
It's tough to time this...
There we go.
Okay, that just kills me.
I don't understand.
Am I soft-locked right now?
Like, what can I do?
I can't...
Go anywhere.
Up!
Maybe if we're fast?
No.
It's wrong with my people?
Let's have a look.
Wait, what?
I'm...
I'm so confused right now.
No, there's no way I gotta go back here, right?
Okay, so I made my way around here.
Anti-clockwise.
Just to get up here.
So I could flip a switch so I could not get back up to the switch?
Is that a jokes on me thing?
Or what?
No!
Okay, we have something here.
I want to mark it on the map, but I can't.
We gotta time this really well.
Oh, wait.
I can actually just...
Oh, it's not that hard, actually.
Yeah.
Oh, close one.
That should be doable.
Uh, wrong way.
I...
Bro!
I am so confused.
Wait, what?
Oh, that's...
Those are stalactites!
Uh...
Nah, bro.
Okay.
I'm scared.
I want to look for food.
This is tur...
Oh!
We got a mammal here!
Hello?
Don't be scared of me!
I want to play a frisbee!
You like slinkies?
How about some music?
Come on!
What...
What's...
What's going on with you?
Alright, I'm gonna save here.
Ring up the people.
Uh...
Oh, he's so scared of me.
Okay.
I'm gonna mark this here.
There is something very...
Weird going on here.
So I went...
Down here.
Oh, maybe something changed down here.
Let me go back downstairs.
Maybe the breakable walls have unbroke themselves.
But how do I get back down?
That shit's locked off now!
Oh my god!
Am I actually softlocked or something?
I don't get it.
This room right here breaks my brain.
I have no clue what is happening.
No clue.
I can't get back up here.
I can't do anything in here.
Oh!
MLG Gamer 360!
No scope!
Fucking crop rotations up in this!
But what the hell is this even?
How will I...
Ha-ha!
What?
That's...
That's impossible.
Wait, we have a safe spot actually.
Hold on.
Ah!
Impossible!
That is impossible.
Buddy!
Maybe the room will reset now.
How do I get down again?
Take me south!
I mean, if I can flip the switch up there, then I'm good.
But I can't.
Scheisse.
That actually...
I think that is the way to get up there.
We just gotta time it correctly.
Ah, that was too early.
Ah, shit.
I'm not gonna have time now.
Ah!
Ah, you bastard!
I can't do it!
I'm not MLG enough for this!
What the hell?
Slinky?
Do you like Slinky's?
Maybe the Slinky is the way?
Brother Man.
I don't understand.
Maybe a Slinky here?
You like that?
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, you know what?
I probably need firecrackers here.
That will do something, right?
That will surely help me out.
Yeah, I don't know.
I've...
I feel like I don't understand that.
Let's go somewhere else.
So there's something over here.
That was locked, right?
Yeah.
We gotta find a switch for that.
And this guy is scared of me, unfortunately.
We may have to find the song of his people and play it for him.
That way he will feel comfortable and everything is right between us.
This place.
Okay.
There's a scary entity in here.
Oh my god.
What?
Okay, there we go.
One more.
He's in here somewhere.
Can I reveal your position with my...
With my song?
Oh yeah!
I hit the spikes again.
Are you kidding me?
Oh!
Yeah.
We did it.
Don't hit me.
Oh my god.
I saw my death coming.
My goodness.
That was so uncomfortable.
Oh, this is nice looking.
These are like Yakuza animals, right?
At least associated with the Yakuza?
What's up, squirrel?
Ah!
Discovered.
I'm...
I'm not here to hurt you.
Let me play you the song.
Ooh!
Fuck that voice!
Oh my god.
That was creepy.
You kidding me?
I am not gonna go that way.
Nuh-uh.
We're gonna put a little marker here called...
Fuck that shit.
FTS.
Moving on.
Oh!
Breakable wall.
Watch.
Karate kick.
Maybe I'll learn a karate kick.
Imagine.
I have legs.
I have no hands, though.
How am I throwing the frisbee?
I guess I'm spitting it?
This guy's gonna be instrumental in my progress somehow.
But I can't prove it.
There it is.
Oh!
Now he serves as a way to...
I see.
Uh-huh.
We found a key!
That is massive.
Good stuff.
Not sure what that will unlock.
Going up.
Oh!
I'm here!
It all leads back, doesn't it?
Okay.
Now, maybe I'll take another quick look down here.
With the scary stuff.
Yeah.
This way, then down and left.
It's crazy how many textures, uh, they're making, uh, this game appear to have.
With these different patterns of colors.
It's really quite impressive.
I really enjoy the environment, Silo!
Oh, okay.
Song?
Play a song.
RAAA!
Nope.
That's not working.
How the fuck are you gonna...
Oh, naa, naa, naa, naa, naa, naa, naa.
Just go!
Oh, oh, I see!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Wow.
No, no way, sir.
Here it comes!
Yo!
Hit the buttons!
The other head is coming!
Yeah, bop, bop, bop, bop!
Down!
DEE!
Wow!
Down!
Left!
I'm stuck!
There we go!
Down, down, down, down, down, down!
There's probably a button here, right?
Button!
Yep, button!
Where's the head?
You can't reach me.
Button time.
DOO!
Away with you.
Ooh!
Back!
That's right.
How do I get out?
Oh, shit!
Nice, I can break it.
Come here!
Dumbass!
See ya!
Wow!
That was cool!
I like that.
Scary, but very cool.
Now I'm gonna frisbee myself.
Hup!
Yeah!
Trix!
Tony Hawk!
Fire X!
And then...
We descend.
Whoop!
Okay.
That's a worm.
Isn't it crazy?
It's like five pixels animated, and you can tell clearly it's a worm.
Blows my mind.
It's like the glass panes in Minecraft, you know?
The reflections on them.
It's just like four pixels, but you can totally tell it's a glass pane.
Our brains are weird.
Pattern recognizers.
What's this?
There's gotta be more here.
That's water.
It looked like a platform to me.
That's also water!
Please!
Pull yourself together!
How did that happen four times?
That is unreal.
Okay.
Continue on right.
And there's a button here.
So, how do we get to that?
Maybe I use my absurdly long tongue.
Maybe I inverse slinky it.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Okay.
Um...
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
I know how to do this.
Oh, it's so smart, actually.
Check it.
Check, check, check, check, check, check.
Mic check, 212.
Hup!
Oh, my...
Oh, really?
I thought that would be perfect.
Uh, maybe here?
Oh, no!
There's a vine in the way!
Short form content!
Uh, let's do...
What should be the symbol for a button?
Maybe the spiral.
That's the symbol for a button.
Because just like a spiral, the button goes round and round, right?
It's a round button, and it goes up and down.
That is cyclic in nature.
Even though a spiral is not really...
Ah, you get the point.
So, I see multiple buttons, actually.
And what they all have in common is, I have no idea how to get to them.
So, my gamer brain is going to assume I'm going to need an upgrade for that.
And, not only that, that upgrade is going to be in that chest right there.
Make me right.
I found a yo-yo!
Yo-yo!
Oh!
The physics!
That's insanity!
That is incredible!
Oh!
Can I use it to...
Sling myself?
No, further.
Haha, this is so good!
I guess the yo-yo doesn't have enough weight to carry me.
Um...
Right.
Cool!
Oh my god!
That doesn't actually make much sense physically, but...
I like it!
Unless it's because the surface is sticky or something?
I don't know what the...
Like, what's going on there?
Yeah, maybe a sticky surface or something.
Is that a button?
No, that's a...
Non-button.
Not a button.
Oh my god.
It's great.
Yeah!
Man!
The slinky!
The...
The yo-yo!
Incredible!
S-plus items.
Loving it!
Now we can remove this marker.
That's satisfying.
Get off.
That is so cool!
I'm gonna...
Fuck up.
Oh wait, there's not an enemy.
It's a friend.
Um...
Right.
Hup!
Look how happy it is to carry me.
Now we...
Let's have a bath.
We're gonna have a bath right here.
Lots of buttons.
Lots of possibilities for yo-yoing.
I like it.
Jump.
Let's have a...
Double bath!
Look at that double bath.
Let's take a break while we double bath.
Five minutes.
I'll see you soon.
Hey guys.
What do you think so far, huh?
I think it's pretty amazing.
I really like the game.
And usually I need some time for it to warm up to me.
But this is already just up my alley.
Pretty cool, huh?
I'm gonna die watching this, but it's good.
What do you mean?
Why would you die?
The gamer is interesting.
Thank you.
Well, I...
You know, I'm just having fun with it.
I think I understand why you don't know what colored lizards are.
Dude, I went on Google...
And I searched for lizards.
And you know what came up?
All the colors of the rainbow.
Great.
That didn't help me at all.
You need to go back to kindergarten?
Maybe.
It's very fun hearing all the wrong animal names.
I don't know a lot about animals.
But I think I'm right, like, 70% of the time.
Lizards are cool.
I guess.
But they have a creepy tongue.
I don't have a favorite animal.
Maybe the penguin.
I like the way they wobble when they walk.
That's the cutest thing.
Except when people wobble.
I only like it when penguins wobble.
When people wobble, it means...
It's probably time to cut back on some food.
That's like the tipping point, you know?
No pun intended.
That's when you know you have gone too far.
That's what I'm afraid of one day.
If I ever end up wobbling, then I know I'm in bad shape.
You know?
Are you actually smart?
I don't know.
I guess I'm pretty average.
I think if you were to draw a bell curve of intelligence of the human population...
I'm probably somewhere around the most average.
Statistically speaking.
I should be.
You like the penguins who vomit explosives?
What?
Maybe that's a reference to something.
I don't know what that means.
Oliver's butt doesn't jiggle when he walks, confirmed.
You got it.
Not yet.
But maybe soon.
It's gonna drain your soul.
Good.
I'm here to do that.
Just like I drained the brain of that one animal.
I'm gonna slurp up your soul.
And consume it.
It's what nourishes me.
It's what keeps me going.
Yes.
How much longer are we streaming today?
I think maybe one and a half hours more.
Then I gotta get some food in me.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Back in the game.
Also, hold on.
Someone sent me a message.
Right.
That was the flashy...
Flashy image setting.
I already did that.
Perfect.
Okay.
I think we've been washing ourselves long enough here.
The double birdbath is working.
Wait.
Why did my character turn black now?
I'm like dark.
Maybe just because it's a dark room.
Wasn't I blue before?
I was blue before.
Blue bird.
Okay.
So now I jump to...
This...
Oh.
Check this.
Ah.
Right.
I already forgot I had the yo-yo.
There we go.
Yo-yo time.
Yo-yo gameplay is best.
Oh.
There we go.
Look at that.
Oh my god.
That's beautiful.
Yeah.
It's like the tongue of that one animal that goes...
Into the ground, you know.
I forget the name of the animal.
But there's an animal that does that.
And I think it sucks up ants or something.
That's like its whole shtick.
I freed another bird.
I see.
Let's see if you turn invisible somewhere.
You don't.
But I can jump up here now and jump on you.
Yeah.
Sick.
I love these types of puzzles.
Let's go on an adventure, bird.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I just had a crazy thought.
Listen.
There's a melody being played right now when these things are moving around.
What if I were to play that melody on my flute?
I'm not going to do it, but imagine.
I presumably need my disc for this.
Why am I jumping down here?
How do I get up there?
Maybe I don't need to.
Let me go over here first.
Have a look.
Right.
I came from here.
Ha ha.
True.
This is a little bit...
Yep.
Okay.
I guess I just go down.
Boop.
Nice.
That chest is mine.
The question is how.
Come on, bird.
You gotta drop me.
It'll be fine.
In fact, let's use a marker for that.
Which marker, you ask?
The chest marker, of course.
Boom.
Except there's gotta be a way to get it now, right?
No way there's not.
Can I hit the...
I cannot hit you.
Yeah.
Get it in there.
I put this yo-yo...
Hey!
I'm doing it.
Something's happening.
Maybe.
No.
Huh.
Oh, I know.
I think I know.
You gotta ride a disc, perhaps?
No.
Okay, I don't know.
Yeah, I can't jump down because the bird will always pick me up.
What just happened?
Oh!
We got an animal here.
I see.
Aha.
Watch this.
We're gonna yo-yo our way through this.
Oh, that's...
That's...
That's a tough one.
There it is!
Now.
Oh no, you don't want to wake up to that?
Come on!
It's closed encounters.
Okay.
Let's go to this one.
That's a kangaroo.
Look at that beating chest.
That's one big heart.
Are you going to be animal?
You're gonna be animal!
What the...
Okay.
Let me soothe you.
Nobody likes my song.
Why are you not reacting?
Okay.
Check this out.
That's so cool.
Hey!
Oh!
I'm too slow!
I'm dead.
Wow!
Oh my god.
Okay.
Whoa!
How on earth are you gonna...
Do that?
Shit.
Do I yo-yo you?
I'm walking the yo-yo.
Walking the dog.
That's a trick.
Oh my god.
Why are you making human sounds?
Slinky.
He likes it!
He liked the song before.
I'm totally lost here.
Can't get down.
There's also a path up here.
We could try going here and just double checking.
What's up here?
Let me put a marker.
That marker is gonna be an animal again.
Right there.
A deadly animal.
Who's out for blood.
That's an animal with a shield and a spear!
You kidding me?
Okay.
How do you like yo-yos?
Yo-yo in your face.
Oh yeah?
Oh, you didn't like that, did you now?
Get yo-yoed, nerd.
Oh, he mad.
I don't think I understand how to control this yo-yo properly.
How do I make it go down?
Without standing there.
Do I have to stand there?
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I get it.
I see.
So when you let go of it, it comes back, of course.
It's a yo-yo.
It makes sense.
Hit him.
And then I gotta hurry down and walk past him, or what?
Go!
Dumbass.
Okay.
Can't reach the button.
Oh, maybe I can reach you.
Oh, I'm terrible.
There we go.
Okay, I gotta be faster.
This yo-yo is really difficult to control.
I could just walk past him, though.
There you go.
Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
I'm not sorry.
Deserved.
A key!
How many do I have?
I got two keys!
Okay.
Very good.
Oh!
You can even do that!
Okay.
Oh, shit.
You're actually coming for my ass.
Don't want you anywhere near me.
Unlock?
Did I just use two keys for that?
Holy shit.
This better be good.
Now, that's not a phone.
That is actually a TNT device.
It's gotta be.
Oh, yeah!
God, those smoke effects, though.
They get me going.
Really neat.
Ah!
Now I'm here...
Okay!
So, we do have a way to get back in here.
I should have trusted.
Ah!
Shit!
Not this again.
I thought you were gone by now.
Oh, my God.
What is that even?
Right.
That leads us up here.
Oh!
Wait a sec.
Oh, I could have just done this all the time.
I guess.
I also see a path on the right.
Maybe.
Let's go back here.
Explore the left side.
I've been here.
Yep.
There's still a door right...
There.
Let's mark it.
Ah, shit.
Which symbol did I use for doors?
I don't remember.
It's gotta be a question mark.
Let's be miscellaneous now.
I love miscellaneous.
It's probably my favorite category.
Ah, shit.
That's right.
Anyway, we made a shortcut, I guess.
We haven't been over here.
Let me check that out.
That's a stork, again.
A hologram of it.
But a large one.
Oh, I didn't even see you.
You were so camouflaged.
Let me...
Ah!
I didn't mean to walk into you.
Dang it.
Where am I?
Okay, I'm not that far off.
I don't want to ring up the people.
They don't know what I'm doing, and that's good.
Keep it a secret.
I don't want to report back unless I have anything to report, you know?
I don't know.
Birdbath.
I'm going to go up here.
This again.
So here.
And then back over here.
Good shit.
Okay.
This shit again.
Um.
What about that chest, huh?
Whoa!
Oh my god!
Dude, I didn't even see that!
I was looking somewhere else.
God damn it.
Um.
Right.
Here.
Can I really not get down there somehow?
Okay, come on.
We gotta play some kind of song here.
You really don't like that?
I don't understand.
I'm gonna try going here.
Light up the place!
I love the flute.
So nice.
Jump up here.
Ah!
Rust egg!
Nice!
Oh shit.
I thought I could jump on the bird.
Jump on the bird.
I can definitely get up there.
Shit.
Oh, I'm so good!
But we mistimed it.
Ah!
Close one!
Why am I trying to do here anyway?
That's a tough one up there.
Yeah, how am I gonna...
Maybe from over here on the right.
There's a chest up there!
We can't leave that behind.
No freaking way.
Doesn't come back.
Ah, too slow.
Ah!
Oh, close!
There's no way!
Actually, I know how to do it.
I'm kind of a dumbass.
I see now.
I see.
I understand.
And...
Go!
Did I make it?
No.
We gotta jump from the right side, then.
But how the hell do I attach to this bird again?
I can't.
What?
Maybe I go back up on the right side and then jump down?
Hopefully the better...
Oh!
That's a sine curve.
With a, uh...
That's a sine curve plus a linear function.
Ah!
Plus a constant!
Amplitude?
What does this middle one do?
Ah!
Okay, okay.
The face.
Oh no, that's not the face.
That's adding the linear function.
This one is...
Amplitude?
Oh god.
This is fitting by hand!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Almost.
Not quite.
Ha ha ha!
Shit!
Ah!
Yeah!
Let me see.
Just want to find the shape.
Not...
That could be it right there.
Oh god.
Shit balls.
Okay, so it's clearly descending.
This is why we have, uh...
Fitting...
Uh...
Fitting algorithms.
Nobody wants to do this by hand.
It sucks.
Ha ha ha!
I mean, it's fun in this game, but...
God damn it!
Can I reverse?
Oh!
I didn't even realize!
Oh shit!
That's probably it then.
Here and then...
Maybe not?
Reverse that.
No.
Dude, I can't figure this out.
That's a rough one!
Yeah...
Hmm...
This is gonna take a while.
I can tell you that right now.
It's not even that...
Big of a range of values I can choose.
Like, how am I not getting this?
That's almost there.
The thing I need here...
I need the...
The face to be a little different.
Motherfucker.
Oh, it's also cool that the door is being lit by the, uh...
Yellow dots.
When I fill them up.
You see that?
That's really neat.
Full detail.
Like, this looks like...
It could work, right?
Now we just need to...
Yeah, but that's the problem.
It's like, this adds...
Hmm.
This, uh...
You know what I mean?
Like, this is the shape.
We just gotta...
Fucking...
Change the face here.
I will never get this.
That is not gonna work.
It's gotta be the other sign.
Actually, that could work.
That's way too much.
Fuck!
I am bad at this.
Give me, like, uh...
An R2 value.
To work from.
Ha ha ha ha.
Or something.
Bro, I can't do it.
I don't know.
Like, what is the...
Is it just a straight line?
Oh, hold on.
Are we...
Am I being fucked with here?
Oh my god!
Those bastards!
It was...
It was such a low amplitude!
I didn't even explore that parameter space at all!
Jade Egg.
I just assumed it would be a high amplitude.
Um...
That's a fish in a pipe, by the way.
It's stuck.
Shark.
In fact, it looks like a shark.
Maybe I yo-yo the shark.
You like yo-yos?
Sir.
Yep!
Hebo!
No?
Okay.
What did I just get in the chest?
I didn't pay attention.
I got an egg.
That's right.
We got an egg.
Wait!
Walk the dog!
In the pipe?
Wait.
Maybe the fish will appreciate some...
Music?
Nobody appreciates my music.
I thought for sure I could walk the dog through here.
You know, through this pipe, and then something would happen on the other side.
That would be a great little puzzle.
I feel like there's some...
Maybe it's just a water bath.
I mean, from the map here, it looks like it's just a bath.
But maybe not everything is as it seems.
This room...
We still haven't figured out how to get to that chest.
But surely I can get back up here.
If I jump on this, and then...
Yeah, yeah.
Good.
Good, good, good, good.
Now we're here.
Now I want to go back up to the left.
And...
Oh, but I can't fall down because of the bird.
Like, no matter what I do, he can't let me fall.
Right.
Do I have a way to accelerate myself somehow?
Oh!
Didn't even see you.
Whoops.
That's annoying.
Surely it's a skill issue here.
I want to turn on a candle here so bad.
Ah, I'm seeing a little platform on the left there.
That could be used for a disc.
So maybe if I fall and hug the wall on the left.
That could be an idea.
Yeah!
I'm so good!
A ruby egg!
Just for me.
Beautiful.
Okay.
What a great little puzzle here, actually.
I actually enjoyed that.
Even though it was frustrating.
Frustrating in a good way, you know?
As all puzzles are.
Not all, but some.
I went the wrong way, didn't I?
We gotta go along here.
Maybe I'll get a swim ability.
Wait, what?
No, we're going up.
Going up.
Not right.
There we go.
Okay.
We could try and go back to...
Okay, you.
You bastard.
I have one HP left.
Will you appreciate my music?
He appreciates us now.
So maybe we're good now?
Are we friends?
Maybe he's okay with me now.
Nope!
Oh my god!
I thought we were bros!
Fucking asshole!
Stabbed me in the back.
With a rusty knife.
I called you my brother.
And then you do that.
Let's go, birdie.
Oh no, I gotta do this again.
That's not that bad, actually.
We gotta deal with the kangaroo.
The answer?
Poo.
Throw poo in his face.
There's no way he's gonna want to deal with me after that.
Jump!
Oh yeah, look at that.
He's gone.
Unbelievable.
What a bastard.
Where did you go, huh?
Whoa.
Yes!
I'll call my parents.
Let them know that I'm having trouble with puzzles.
They can comfort me.
I'm going up.
That's a...
Mouse in a hamster wheel.
Dude, we have to make him run the other way.
So this goes down.
Watch.
Bonk the lamps.
Here.
I got squished!
I'm not the good kind!
Fuck, that's scary!
Wow!
Wait, that is a giant teddy bear.
Wait, is this even possible?
So if I go here, here, here, here, here, here, and then chest...
Yeah, it's possible.
Run!
Oh my god!
Is that a cat I hear?
Wait, do I have time?
If I jump now...
Oh, wait, don't stand there.
If I jump...
No, there's no way I have time.
We gotta go...
Oh!
I hate that!
Please don't squish me.
That is terrifying.
There's a cat somewhere!
It needs help.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
There's no way to get to that chest.
And go.
Boom!
Man.
Go!
Okay.
Oh, yeah!
Okay, this game is difficult.
I definitely underestimated it a little bit in the beginning.
Okay, lock in now.
No more bullshit.
You can do this.
It's easy.
Dude, look at the platforms.
They even have a little creature pointing right and then left.
You see that?
I think I'm right about the wheel.
Well, that chest seems impossible to get to.
We gotta...
I don't wanna lock...
Lock in.
It's not that hard.
You can do this.
Just focus.
Think about the cat that's meowing.
It needs her help.
You can't be failing it.
Wait, I know how to do this.
I know how to do it.
I'll show you in a second here.
I'm gonna die.
Ah, I'm gonna die.
That was on purpose, because I wanted to get back.
You'll see what I mean.
And go!
Yeah!
It's a dessert egg!
Mmm.
Eat it later.
With some flan.
Go!
What?!
Oh, I had to jump.
I thought the level changed on me.
Eh...
I should've just gone there, actually.
Now we wait.
No more messing around.
Jump!
Okay.
Go!
Now.
As soon as it's gone, we go.
Wow!
Ho-ho-ho!
That is some scary shit!
Wait a sec.
Right.
I see what to do.
I know.
Oh my god!
That was too close!
Woo!
All right!
All right.
Hey!
I knew it!
You see that?
Nailed it.
So now...
We're gonna go here.
And there was a path down below.
Whoops.
Nope, that's fine.
What?
Can I stand on that?
I can't.
Okay, okay, okay.
Well, I can't get to the right.
There's another fish in a little tube!
I feel bad for that fish.
Quick thinking now.
Quick thinking.
Didn't mean to do that.
It was a mistake.
Whoopsie-dopsie.
Yeah!
Look at me!
Oh!
Okay, I thought I had enough height there.
Yep!
Shit!
Man, this game is...
Wait, what was that?
Oh, there was a little platform down there.
I didn't even see that.
Okay, I'm dying a lot, actually.
My prediction of not dying in this game was hilarious now.
I really...
I really thought it was good.
No!
Oh my god!
I must be at like 50 deaths already.
Yup!
Yeah!
Why am I here?
Why did I jump up here?
Oh, I know.
I know, I know, I know.
I know.
Oh, but this is tough.
This is a...
How on earth are you gonna...
Oh, that's...
That's really...
That's a rough one.
Also, notice on the right we have a little symbol.
The antechamber.
That's what that looks like.
If you don't know what that means, don't think too hard about it.
It's a square with a center in it.
I'm guessing if the, um, the hamster runs the other way, then these are gonna reverse.
Right?
That's the prediction here.
What if I play a tune?
Nobody cares.
Nobody cares about my deep and impactful song.
Well, shit.
I...
Man, I don't know what to do here.
I'm actually kind of...
I mean, I was gonna bounce one of these back and forth, but I can't do that and then get back up.
Right?
No, there's no way.
Also, it breaks on them anyway, so it's not gonna bounce back and forth.
How do I get back, even?
I guess you can technically do it.
Shit.
That's crazy.
Ah!
It's unreal.
Okay.
Now what?
Am I gonna get squished?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh!
Now I'm here!
That's actually fitting.
Okay, well, so this place down here is definitely a mystery.
Also, it looks like it's gonna lead me back to this room over here.
Weird.
Alright.
What about Daddy Kang?
Is he back?
He's not.
I'm gonna go up again.
Well, that was kind of a weird little path we took there.
Okay, we gotta press that button.
And it looks like the only way to get there is to go higher up and then fall down.
We can do that.
Maybe.
Oh, can we?
Yes, we can.
Maybe I missed the path up here.
What did I miss?
What?
I didn't even see.
Oh, I guess I was not positioned correctly.
Okay, so that...
Okay.
Now it's going down.
But that doesn't help me in any way, right?
Like, I can't get back up, of course.
Can I change the direction anywhere?
Or just down there?
What if I hit a wheel up here?
Oh!
God damn it.
Bro, I don't know what to do.
What?
There we go.
Here.
Okay.
Oh, I...
Ah!
Crazy.
Wow.
Okay, now.
Scan the environment.
What happens if I squish my bowl?
Probably nothing you want to do, really.
Alright.
Now I'm here.
It looks like there's a path.
Maybe down there on the left?
I can break that?
Can I shoot it?
Oh!
My God!
Wait.
Ah, it's hard hitting that note.
Ah!
I fucked it up.
It's very inaccurate.
What if I... Okay, that's actually much easier.
If you do the, um... Oh, yeah.
So we're gonna do...
What?
Really?
What's the last one?
I can't tell what that is.
Maybe it's the other way?
Maybe you have to guess the last one.
God damn it.
These arrows are definitely important.
I'm gonna write it down.
I didn't actually prepare any notes taking software thing.
Because I didn't think I'd need it.
I'm gonna use a good old notepad.
We'll see how intensive notes are in this game.
Maybe they're not intensive.
Okay.
Wait, that's not... Use a pencil.
That's the only reliable fucking method.
There.
Arrow.
Down right.
And then... What is that last one?
Right.
Okay.
Maybe try it the other way.
Hmm.
I don't know what's going on there.
Check it out.
What if I were to... Okay, never mind.
Well, that's a secret.
Oh, wait a minute.
That is the same room I was in earlier.
The one where I theorized breakable walls.
Remember that?
I gotta get down.
Wait, how did I... Oh, right.
And now... Oh, shit.
I don't know.
I gotta get to that button.
Which means I gotta press...
Wait, what?
Does this button... Open one of these doors?
Or do I need to press a button to open one of these doors?
That's a question, isn't it?
Actually, wait a sec.
It almost looks like... There's a secret on the left here?
This area is gonna be the end of me.
I'm so confused.
Especially this bottom part down here is really messing with me.
Let me try this, uh...
Melody again.
Um... We're gonna do...
Yeah!
Okay, okay.
Now, I did discover... This head, didn't I?
But why couldn't I do anything with it?
Open up!
Open your mouth!
Okay.
Where's my, um... Okay.
Is this the same?
Looks like it.
Wait.
Hello?
There we go.
Well, I don't know.
What was the point here?
Alright, let's try and go back a bit.
I'm deb... Okay, let's see the map here.
So... This is the hub area down there.
And it looks like there's a flame right next to it.
So I guess by opening the animal on the top right, we're gonna get access to it.
I forgot what this symbol meant on there.
The map that I put here.
To the right.
Let's check that out once more.
Alright, so these guys need to be woken up.
Come here.
Follow me.
Brian... Oh yeah!
So we can remove that.
That's satisfying.
Gone.
Right.
And we opened this mouth by using the melody.
Did we?
Or did I hit him with the disc?
Uh... No, it was the melody.
It was the melody.
Because we've got the melody over here on the left.
Yeah.
Uh... I will grab that.
And then I'll show it go this way.
Okay.
Let's go to the egg room.
I'm here.
Look at all those eggs.
That's a lot of eggs.
Not enough to open a door, though.
Oh, I can see.
So 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I need 16 eggs to open the next one.
And I have 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13.
Three more.
I see.
Okay.
I can go find those.
Oops.
Should be too hard.
There's also a path here.
Right there.
And to get to that, we gotta go through here.
I forgot what was going on there.
Let's check that out again.
Down.
And you know what?
I'm gonna save the game here.
Bring up the people.
Call my uncle.
I know what an uncle is.
And now we're here, we gotta go left.
Bunny eating grass.
Oh.
Here.
Yo-yo.
No?
I don't mind picking up some firecrackers.
Besides, wasn't this the area where we could light a candle or something?
There was an area in the very beginning.
Oh, here it is!
Oh, shit!
Wow!
Didn't even have a chance to react there.
That's unfair.
Kind of funny that I set the candle thing and then it happened right after.
Oh, so that deletes him forever, I guess.
Cool.
See, now I'm thinking, though, with all my newfound strength and abilities, can I do things that I couldn't do before?
The very beginning is intriguing to me.
Something was going on there.
Maybe it somehow connects to the hub area.
I think this is the breakable wall symbol I made.
Is it?
No, it's not.
This was something else.
I forgot what that was.
Oh, a door that I could open.
But I couldn't open it yet.
That was the symbol for that.
Yeah, 13x.
Oh, I can also just check here, of course.
Instead of just counting.
Whoops.
Wait a minute.
Almost on the right.
Down here.
Up again.
I'm kind of getting FOMO about the early areas now.
Right.
How do I get up there?
Oh, I'm an idiot.
We use a disc, of course.
No, we can't, because there's vines.
Crap.
So we're not doing that.
I'm going to go back up here, though.
This area seems important.
It's a huge area.
And there's all these animals.
There's the underwater sea creature.
What about this creature here?
You don't like any of these.
You don't care about the fireworks.
I wonder if this board is changing over time.
Something else.
I had a question mark on the right.
Let's investigate that again.
This button.
I may not have pressed that.
You know how I know?
Because it's not pressed.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah.
All right.
Wait, can I...
Break it all.
Oh, that's so good.
No thanks.
Can I scare you with my...
Power.
Get out of my face.
My god.
Ah, we gotta yo-yo this.
So good.
Ah!
Whoop, boop!
Oy, you got me.
You bastard.
Right?
Found a match!
Very good.
Now, how do I...
Come on, reach something!
Yeah, no.
Okay, maybe not.
But how am I gonna get down there?
It's too dark to see the map.
Hmm.
I refuse to leave.
What?
Oh, okay.
I don't know.
Doesn't do anything.
Shit.
Okay.
They're not that scary, actually, now that you...
know what to do.
Now, we gotta, of course, mark this down here.
There's a chest.
Right there.
And I think I'm gonna access it from here.
So, you know what?
Let's do that now.
I see a potential path.
Also, there's something going on up there with the bunny.
Maybe I was there already.
Don't get distracted.
There's something in the bottom left here.
Oh.
What?
Wait, can I just destroy these?
Yeah!
Break it all!
Just break that shit!
Oh, so much better.
There it is.
A planet egg!
Planet Earth?
That's 14.
Very cool.
Making progress here.
Dude, making progress in this game is so satisfying.
Oh, and now I'm here.
Right.
Okay.
Good shit.
We can remove that chest now.
That was not it.
It was that one.
Gone.
Then I marked a question mark over there.
Let's go investigate that!
Now that we have the yo-yo...
Oh.
I may have to do a little bit of something again here that I've already done.
Right, there was a big mystery with this whole area.
Just...
Oh, shit.
Don't overthink it.
Just jump down, jump down.
It's fine, it's fine.
Yeah, just like that.
Good.
Opens that.
Gives me some food.
And now that I click that button...
This changed up here.
Yes.
Okay.
Then we go right...
This area is breaking my brain a little bit.
Right.
And that's why I had to do this now.
Because I...
Yeah.
I remember.
Whoop!
Look at that.
Wait.
Right.
There we go.
Why is there a light up there?
Yeah, just break all of this.
I hope this stays broken forever and not like...
If I reset or save, hopefully it doesn't...
You know?
Oh, that's so good.
I can hold it!
Much better.
Wow!
Promise egg...
In these trying times.
I shall...
Gladly accept that.
Very cool.
We gotta be destroying all of this now.
Absolutely everything.
Whoop!
All of it needs to go...
About almost everything.
Even if I could destroy the stuff up there, would I even...
Want to?
It doesn't look like there's anything below.
Okay.
Then we had some breakable walls down there.
Allegedly.
We can check that out later.
Now this...
This little...
Area here...
Is such a mindfuck.
They don't care about the yo-yos at all.
Or the slinky.
Or the hinky dinky.
What about this?
They don't give a F...
About that.
Yeah.
I need some kind of item...
To go through here.
I also see a chest.
So I'm gonna note it down.
Is it still too dark?
Is this still too dark?
Wow.
Mark that down.
Chest right...
There.
Beautiful.
Okay.
What next?
Also, maybe I should indicate like...
Oh, we can remove this marker too.
Gone.
I want to indicate that we need a new item to progress.
But it's also dangerous to assume that.
It could be a skill issue right now...
That I can't make my way through that little puzzle area.
Who knows?
I'm gonna assume that I am missing an item.
Because I just don't accept that I have a skill issue.
I don't.
I don't accept that.
Uh...
Yeah, this ain't gonna work.
We gotta wait.
Now.
Oh!
Bastards.
They got me there.
I forgot their movement.
Wah!
Close one.
Now, while I'm up here...
Wait a sec.
I can destroy some things.
No, I want to do that, right?
Let's open the doors.
Opens the doors downstairs.
Oh yeah, break it.
Nice!
Break them all.
The sounds they make when they break.
So good.
Now, while I'm here...
Now we can progress from here.
I think I understand this room now.
I won't say I'm a master...
at that room, but I understand it.
Also...
Wah!
Thought maybe I could damage you with that.
I couldn't.
But, you know what?
All these spikes...
they gotta be hiding something.
Right.
I'm not afraid of ya.
I am actually a little bit afraid of ya.
CHEST!
Back...
tracking...
as always...
is paying off.
My god.
This is impossible.
How can you do this?
Oh god!
Nah, bro.
Fuck that.
Why won't I throw?
Oh, it's my...
I thought it was a mouse running back and forth.
It was my own...
jalapeno.
Fuck!
I was so confused!
I thought it was the mouse going back and forth all this time.
Oh god.
There's no way.
Yes!
Yo-ho-ho!
Bubble egg!
It belongs to me.
It's mine.
Oh!
Oh-ho-ho-y!
Close one.
Yep!
Oh, okay.
Calm down now.
Jesus!
I just want to break these, okay?
Calm down!
How?
Wait, how did I do this before?
Did I just jump it?
Or what?
Oh god!
That was stupid.
How many eggs?
16 eggs!
Let's go back.
Where are we?
Who am I?
What's my name?
Up here!
And where am I?
I'm here.
And to get up there, how...
How do I do?
I see how I do.
I see it.
Go from here.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, you're gonna come back?
You're not.
Okay.
Heey!
Nii!
I had it.
What?
Yes!
But that happens next time.
Next time...
We shall explore the second door in Animal Well.
Next time.
That was a good spot to end.
Now I have something cool to look forward to.
Also, look at the bunny on the left.
It's looking all cute and innocent.
The one on the right looks like it just murdered your family and you're next.
Why is it giving me this look?
It's giving me sick looks.
Cheers.
Oh, yeah.
God, I love this music.
I kind of wish there was more music in the game.
I mean, there is some.
Here and there.
But it ends when you transition to other areas.
I want more music.
What's up, guys?
You forgot to save?
Ah, shit.
Ah, it's fine.
I'll know what to do next time.
It wasn't that long ago since I saved.
It'll be fine.
Ah, it'll be fine.
What's done is done.
I'll remember exactly what to do.
You'll see.
In fact, I don't mind doing it again just to remind myself.
In fact, I did it on purpose.
I knew it wasn't going to save.
Dude, the exploration in this game is so much fun.
Really nicely done.
And it really rewards you, too, every time.
Finding chests here and there, breaking objects, seeing this and that.
It's so cool.
Good F.
Good egg cliffhanger.
Jesus.
An egg hanger.
Isn't that a real object?
Like an egg hanger?
I've heard about that before.
Yo, Oliver.
The song of your people that you played on flute.
Was this Billie Eilish?
No, no, it wasn't.
It was the, uh...
The tone used to communicate with the aliens in...
Close Encounters of the Third Kind.
Come on, guys.
Get in the game.
Unless I misplayed it.
Maybe I misremembered how that goes.
So if Billie Eilish used it, she stole it from that movie.
What do you think of the Grave Hound?
I think it was scary at first.
But then it was okay when I could throw a disc at it and it could play with it.
Oh, then we're gonna get copyrighted.
If that gets copyrighted, me playing that melody in this game, that's...
Come on, there's no way.
You cannot remember Close Encounters that well?
Man, that movie's so good.
It's also really funny.
You got all the animals wrong?
No!
You got it wrong.
Listen.
As Feynman said, it doesn't matter what you call things.
As long as you understand their function.
What they're good for.
The inner workings of it.
That's what's important.
That's the essential part of understanding.
Putting labels on things may make you look like you know a lot, but you don't know anything.
Remember that.
Now, you may be able to list off all the different species that exist.
But unless you can explain to me how exactly a bee works and why it spreads its pollen or whatever, I don't know anything about bees.
But you know.
Or flowers.
I don't know anything about those two, actually.
Dolphins and penguins are not the same?
I know.
Duh!
He has that dog in him.
Yeah!
I think that some of that dog rubbed off on me when I encountered it.
So now it's inside of me.
Oh my god, that's...
I got that dog in me.
I haven't seen Bee Movie.
Just watch a Honey Nut Cheerios ad to learn about bees.
This was a fun stream.
I'm glad you enjoyed it, Plantaroo!
You look forward to it?
I hope it didn't...
Or I guess it lived up to it then.
The expectation you had.
I had a lot of fun with it.
As always, I always underestimate games before I play them because...
I'm, you know, I'm the type of guy that goes into McDonald's and I order the same thing every time.
Because I know I like it.
I'm not very adventurous with my, you know, trying new things.
And if it wasn't for streaming, I probably wouldn't have played a lot of these games.
Because you were suggesting it, you were saying it's good and all that, but...
If it was just me, I probably would have stuck to the games I know, you know, like StarCraft and all that.
And just kept playing those.
So I'm really happy to break out of my comfort zone with all these different games and getting these new experiences.
So in a way, the streaming has opened the world of possibilities for me.
When it comes to trying different games.
It's awesome.
Bee Movie Discord Watch Party?
That's...
That sounds horrible.
It sounds like a horrible movie.
I don't know.
I haven't seen it.
It's a movie about bees?
What do you mean?
Would you have played Outer Wilds on your own?
Yeah, actually.
I think so.
It was just...
It was just the spur of the moment to decide to record it and try to put it on YouTube.
I was making YouTube videos here and there for some time.
And that one just took off.
And then it all started from there.
It was crazy.
But I only wanted to play Outer Wilds because it was like everyone was talking about it.
Including some of my real-life friends.
They were really egging me on to play it, you know?
Like, that game more than anything, I think, people were just raving about.
Egging?
Yeah, yeah.
You heard that right.
I think you would enjoy Type Help.
It's 5 hours for basic playthrough and 7.30 for completionist run.
That's very specific.
7.30?
Not 7.20 or 7.40?
There's no way I'm going to hit any of those times.
Everyone is different, right?
That is such a weird time.
But I believe you.
Let me note it down.
Type Help.
I'll put it on my backlog, okay?
In fact, I do want to play shorter games like that.
It's kind of nice to have some short games played, you know?
I've been playing a lot of long games lately.
Okay, Type Help is now in my backlog.
Thank you for that suggestion.
The cover is just a CD with a poster on it that says Type Help.
Interesting.
I guess we'll see what that's all about at some point.
Would you have watched YouTube if you didn't upload videos?
What do you mean?
I've always been using YouTube.
It's pretty much my social media platform that I use.
What do you enjoy most about Animal Well?
The exploration.
Just the feeling of finding hidden areas and, you know?
I love that.
I also enjoy the puzzle aspects.
They're not too difficult.
They're also not too easy, so it's like a sweet spot for me.
They're simple to the point where it's not too simple and it still makes me feel like a genius when I solve them.
And that's a good thing.
That means you nailed your puzzles.
Thoughts on Swedish people?
I love them.
I love all my northern brothers.
Yeah, Cocoon is also on my backlog.
Apparently made by the same people that did Inside?
Or not quite.
One of them, I think, made that.
He broke off from Playdead and decided to make Cocoon, right?
So I have some expectations, some high expectations for that.
Thoughts on Latvian people?
I don't know much about Latvian people.
You guys love potatoes, right?
We do too in Denmark, so I guess that makes us brothers.
So I guess I love you guys.
Norway?
Nice.
Wait, greetings times too.
From your significant other or maybe a friend?
Lorelei and the laser eyes is also on my list.
I actually almost put that on my poll for the next game to play.
I was just going through the whole list, right?
And picking things.
It's because it sounded a little absurd and that was kind of fun.
Is Nier Automata a long game or a short game?
It's like a it's an Eastern game, right?
Meaning there's all these scantily clad women in it that you know it's a little cringy with that stuff isn't it?
It's a long one.
Next Animal Well stream?
Very soon.
Because I am kind of liking this I gotta say.
I like it a lot.
And I'm gonna keep playing it.
Medium to long I'd say.
It's not just anime booty.
But why is there an anime booty anyway?
I saw some gameplay from it many many years ago and all I saw was someone running around in a character or with a character where you could see her butt and I'm like what is this?
Why?
It's so oh man I sound like such an old man now.
It's so objectifying.
Old man.
It's just it's always been cringe to me that sort of stuff.
Do not check the only other streamer of Animal Well on Twitch.
Maybe we should rate them here at the end.
What do you think?
People are drawn in for the booty then stay for the story and world building.
Okay.
I see the sales tactic.
I guess I do know why they do it.
But part of me also thinks that they're kind of hurting themselves with it.
Like there's plenty of examples of games that don't need to do that to draw in people.
Time has shown that if you make a good game people will play it and will tell other people about it.
And it will spread from there.
You don't need that stuff.
And it just feels a little shallow to me that you would go for those tactics, right?
When all you had to do was make a good game and just trust.
Animal Well does it.
Did you see the main character's little butt?
Okay, you're right.
I gotta say I actually I saw that.
And I and I liked it.
People just kind of just get desenticized to it?
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, I'm gonna play it one day, probably.
I'll definitely check it out.
And if it's not for me, I'll just stop playing it.
But who knows?
Maybe it'll draw me in and the story will be amazing.
And who knows?
Maybe the butts will win me over.
I don't know what L3...
Oh!
No, I haven't seen that online lion.
I haven't really been following that stuff lately.
What happened?
Butts happened.
Apparently there's a little butt in this game that was wiggling and I didn't see it.
But it was there.
I really like that you only play the games for yourself.
Makes your content very special.
Yeah, at least I'm trying to.
I mean, of course you can't get around the fact that I'm streaming it and I'm talking out loud.
Which is something I wouldn't do if I was just sitting by myself.
So in a way you can't really get that pure experience unless I sit there in silence, right?
And that's not really super entertaining to watch either.
So it's a fine balance to strike, I think.
But like I've said before talking out loud also does something else to me which is it internalizes my thoughts a little more clearly.
But it can also detract from my train of thought.
a lot of times I find myself saying something and because of the act of, you know, moving my mouth and creating words and sounds that will distract me from my train of thought and I'll get lost.
That doesn't happen as much when I play alone.
You know, I know there's a meme about me being blind and missing things here and there.
A lot of that has to do with me talking aloud I think.
And I am thinking about my sentences as well because it's not my native language.
It's a subtle effect but it does have an influence on me.
Yeah, definitely plan to rue.
Do you usually create words and thoughts?
Wait, what?
I mean, I like to think that I use my brain at times but who knows?
I could be wrong.
I could be wrong on that.
Gotta train that parallel processing.
Yeah, I need that brain implant that makes me smart in 20 years.
Streamer blindness is very common.
I have a theory on that, Dr. Quack Selber.
The streamer isn't blind.
It's the fact that of course he's streaming so he's gonna be a little more distracted than usual because he's doing the whole streaming putting on a performance as well at the same time.
But I think the most important part is that there's a whole audience of people watching the screen not having to control the character and are free to look anywhere on the monitor you know that will automatically make you see things that the streamer wouldn't see because they're playing the game.
And I bet all my potatoes that when you guys play games by yourself if you had people watching you they would notice a million things you were missing as well.
Something you didn't even realize was happening.
That's my theory I could be wrong but I think I'm right.
I pass more perception checks when I watch.
Yeah, yeah.
And also statistically if you have 300 people or 200 people watching your stream there's always going to be someone pointing something out that you missed, right?
I'm not taking it too serious Vabbitraven.
It's all good.
I know it's all in good fun.
We all have our diorite.
True.
That's true.
I actually did Google or go on YouTube and went what is diorite?
like maybe a couple weeks ago or something because I wanted to know about the stone itself.
I was curious at this point, you know?
And I found a video.
I watched it and I left a comment.
I was like, yeah, this was short and concise and I now understand what diorite is.
Because there's been this mystery all this time like all memes aside, I didn't know what it actually was, you know?
Like, but now I do.
Yeah, yeah.
guys, thank you for watching.
I'm going to go eat food and yeah, that's it.
I have nothing more to say.
Thank you all for being here and subscribing.
I've gotten so many subscribers today.
It's insanity.
So many gifted subs as well and thank you to everyone who also subscribed.
Just personally, it's really quite something.
Thank you.
Have a wonderful evening, okay?
Bye-bye.